<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cole Family</title>
    <link>https://www.colefamily.page/</link>
    <description>  Cole Family</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.colefamily.page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hampshire and Vermont Pt 2</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-10-13/nh-vermont.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-10-13/nh-vermont.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;southern-new-hampshire-aug-21-sep-4&#34;&gt;Southern New Hampshire (Aug 21 - Sep 4)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;nh.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;nh&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our second taste of New Hampshire, we stayed in an RV park in New Boston. It&amp;rsquo;s a small town of almost 6k people, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t have as many stores/restaurants as you&amp;rsquo;d expect for that population size. The RV Park is really big and has 2 playgrounds, which Ezri insisted we visit often. We also visited nearby Milford, a town of about 15k, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t really speak to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;new_boston_castle.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;new_boston_castle&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;new_boston_breakfast.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;new_boston_breakfast&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;milford.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;milford&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also drove out to Concord, the nearby big city. It has a lot of great amenities, and we visited the McAuliffe-Shepard Discovery Center together. They are space focused and even have a Planetarium show. We had tried a planetarium show about a year ago, but Ezri got too scared in the dark and we had to leave within minutes of the show starting. This time, she made it through the entire 45 minute show, and really enjoyed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;concord_street.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;concord_street&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;concord_arch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;concord_arch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rocket.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rocket&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rocket_ezri_mom.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rocket_ezri_mom&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_astronaut.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_astronaut&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we were in the area, the County Faire took place in nearby Hopkinton. We started by looking at the livestock, we really enjoyed seeing all the different breeds of chickens. They also had a monster truck show that we were considering attending, but were worried about the noise level. We lucked out that our ferris wheel ride was timed perfectly to get a free peek, and we were able to confirm it was entirely too loud for Ezri. We&amp;rsquo;ll need to invest in some serious ear protection for her in order to see one up close. Ezri rode a few rides, and went through 2 fun houses. She also insisted on eating 2 root beer floats and a bag of cotton candy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;fair_car.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;fair_car&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;fair_ferris.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;fair_ferris&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;fair_tractor.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;fair_tractor&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our top choice in the state is Keene, which has about 23k people. We wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be able to find land within the city limits, but in one of the surrounding towns about 10 minutes away. They have a great downtown, good running and cycling communities, and a good sized farmer&amp;rsquo;s market. The schools in Keene itself range from 4 out of 10 to 6 out of 10, but the rules vary in the surrounding towns on whether they attend Keene or another school district.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;keene_street.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;keene_street&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;keene_pizza.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;keene_pizza&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we were near Claremont New Hampshire again, we stopped to visit some amazing homesteaders running a small farm called &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.winterstreetfarm.com/&#34;&gt;Winter Street Farm&lt;/a&gt; on the way to Springfield Vermont. They have a three year head-start on a lot of the things we plan to do once we settle down, so it was great to learn about things like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.visitnh.gov/agriculture/farm-to-fork/csa&#34;&gt;CSA (Community Supported Agriculture)&lt;/a&gt; and what to look for in land. They definitely gave us some great information and tried to convince us that this area of New Hampshire was the place to be! We would love to end up in the same area as them to hang out more in the future. Unfortunately we forgot to take pictures of their farm, but here are some pictures of Springfield.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;springfield_vt.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;springfield_vt&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;springfield_vt2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;springfield_vt2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;western-vermont-sep-4-sep-18&#34;&gt;Western Vermont (Sep 4 - Sep 18)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;vt_vaccines.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;vt_vaccines&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our second stay in Vermont, we were in an RV park in Leicester (pronounced Lester), which doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a real town center. Just 5 mins to the south though, is Brandon, which is a town of just under 4k people. They have a pretty good downtown, and a nice farmer&amp;rsquo;s market. The schools in the area are not the best, with elementary getting a 4 out of 10 and high school getting a 2 out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;brandon.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;brandon&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;brandon2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;brandon2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;brandon_water.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;brandon_water&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main town we were looking forward to checking out, Middlebury, is a small town of over 8k people. They have a great downtown with a beautiful river running through it. We talked to a young family at a cafe overlooking the water that just love living there, and Ezri found a giant Adirondack chair to play on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;chair.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;middlebury&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;middlebury_church.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;middlebury_church&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;middlebury_water.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;middlebury_water&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also drove to the elementary school to use the playground, and met a mom and daughter, Sarah and Attalyn, that we really get along well with. We met up with them again to take a hike on a local trail, and grabbed A&amp;amp;W together afterwards. If we end up in this area, it&amp;rsquo;s nice to know we already have a few friends. The schools in the area are pretty nice, ranging between 5 out of 10 and 8 out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;vt_friends.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;vt_friends&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nearby is Vergennes, with a population of 2,500. It has a cute downtown with very nice people. Vergennes also has a river running through it, with some really pretty falls. With being smaller, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have as much selection in the downtown as Middlebury, but it is still very walkable. The schools in the area are decent, with elementary scoring 3 out of 10 and high school 6 out of 10.&lt;img src=&#34;vergennes.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;vergennes&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;vergennes2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;vergennes2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;vergennes3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;vergennes3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another nearby town is Bristol, with a population of almost 4k people. We also really like the downtown, and got talking to one of the shop owners who is on the town planning committee. It was really great to talk to someone so passionate about the direction of the town, and hear about the ideas they are pushing for, like increased infrastructure to support cycling and pedestrians. Another interesting thing in Bristol is the Village Co-housing &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bristolcohousing.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.bristolcohousing.com/&lt;/a&gt;. It&amp;rsquo;s a concept we&amp;rsquo;ve come across a couple times before, but it&amp;rsquo;s basically a group of families that live on the same land in their own houses, but with shared outdoor and large gathering space. We discovered the local toy shop owner lives in the Co-housing, and they sometimes have short term apartment space available. If we decide to return to this area, we&amp;rsquo;ll be checking into whether or not we can stay there for a bit. The schools in Bristol are good, the elementary scored 4 out of 10 and high school 5 out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bristol.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bristol&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In general, around Vergennes, Middlebury, and Bristol, there is a lot of infrastructure in place for cycling, and everywhere we looked there were cyclists and runners. Since the more runners and cyclists, the safer it is to get out there, it&amp;rsquo;s something we&amp;rsquo;re probably going to weigh heavily in our decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;vermont_bridge.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;vermont_bridge&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lake_champlain.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lake_champlain&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &amp;lsquo;big city&amp;rsquo; in the area is Rutland, with a population of about 20k people (there&amp;rsquo;s 2 Rutlands so I added the pops together). There&amp;rsquo;s a regional airport, and the biggest farmer&amp;rsquo;s market we&amp;rsquo;ve ever been to. Ezri got a snow cone that was made by a girl hand cranking out the ice, and we got some mead to try as well. They have your standard big city stuff, and a pretty nice downtown. There&amp;rsquo;s a makerspace and a children&amp;rsquo;s museum that we didn&amp;rsquo;t make it out to see, if we go back through the area we&amp;rsquo;ll probably stop in for both of those. It&amp;rsquo;s definitely a larger city feel than we want to live in, but great to have as a nearby amenity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rutland.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rutland&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rutland_farmersmarket.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rutland_farmersmarket&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_snowcone_rutland.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_snowcone_rutland&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;next-up&#34;&gt;Next Up&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next stop is Ithaca New York on the way to our holiday destination.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mid-Coast Maine</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-09-15/maine.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-09-15/maine.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;maine2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;maine2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first stop in Maine was in Ellsworth, which is a town of about 8k people. While it has a pretty nice downtown, it&amp;rsquo;s also one of the only bridges in the area, so there&amp;rsquo;s almost always terrible traffic. I also didn&amp;rsquo;t have the best experience with running in the area, too many cars wouldn&amp;rsquo;t give me room even on the less busy roads with no shoulder. Due to it being on the way to Acadia National Park, a good amount of that traffic is from tourists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ellseworth.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ellseworth&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Acadia, we drove down to Acadia and Bar Harbor, and were amazed at just how busy it was, even on a weekday. We stopped at a beach and let Ezri play on the rocks, though we couldn&amp;rsquo;t find much sea life other than the snails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bar_harbor_snails.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bar_harbor_snails&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bar_harbor2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bar_harbor2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also drove up to Bangor, the big city nearby with 32k people and Stephen King&amp;rsquo;s hometown. It has a nice downtown but not the acreage for the price we&amp;rsquo;re looking for of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bangor.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bangor&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A town that really stood out to us is Belfast. With about 7k people, it&amp;rsquo;s not too large, and is right on the Bay. They have a lot of community events, there&amp;rsquo;s a game shop that has an after school event with food provided, and everyone we talked to is very active in trying to make things better. The schools aren&amp;rsquo;t rated as highly as some other places we&amp;rsquo;ve looked at, 3-4 out of 10, but digging deeper into those ratings it&amp;rsquo;s due to there being almost half of the students living in poverty. We&amp;rsquo;ve noticed as we look at the school ratings that kids in poverty just don&amp;rsquo;t perform as well, which makes a lot of sense, and isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily something that would scare us away from an area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;belfast_dt.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;belfast_dt&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;belfast_chair.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;belfast_chair&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We came out to Belfast a second time later in our travels, as it was almost exactly halfway between the two places we stayed, and attended &amp;lsquo;Belfast Harbor Days&amp;rsquo;. There were a good number of booths, but I ended up spending almost the entire time at the children&amp;rsquo;s booth where they had a lot of bubble toys. It was run by the lady who owns the local Montessori school, which is something we are considering for Ezri. The approach of Montessori seems like it would be really compatible with her learning style. For some reason, both times we went to Belfast, we got drenched in sudden, heavy rain and had to run for cover. On the second time, we stopped to help with an overturned table and umbrella, which definitely contributed to how soaked we got. I tease James that maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a sign that the town doesn&amp;rsquo;t want us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lincoln.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lincoln&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A little ways south from Belfast along the coast is Camden. It&amp;rsquo;s a small town of about 5k people, but tends to be more of a tourist destination than Belfast. It was very busy when we were there, so it didn&amp;rsquo;t appeal quite as much as Belfast did. The school system is mostly shared with Rockport that is to the south, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t have much of a downtown, so if we were to choose this area we could settle in either place. The area has a reputation of being a bunch of rich kids, and I think that is also reflected in the school rating, as the percent of kids in poverty is only 25%. The schools are well rated, scoring 6-7 out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;camden.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;camden&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even further south is Rockland. It&amp;rsquo;s a town of a little over 7k people, and has a good downtown, but like Camden, we found it was too busy for our tastes. The elementary school is rated 3 out of 10 and the high school is 7 out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rockland.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rockland&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rockland2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rockland2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our second stop was in Nobleboro, which is right next to Damariscotta. We expected to like Damariscotta, but once we saw it in person the downtown was too small. We liked the RV park we were at, it&amp;rsquo;s another place where most people there stay seasonally and know each other really well. They had a massive bonfire, and had live music every weekend. Ezri also got to make a lobster picture with her foot in an art event they had. They are also right on a lake, so one day we rented a canoe and spent some time out on the water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;damariscotta.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;damariscotta&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;nobleboro.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;nobleboro&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another town that really stood out to us is Bath. At just over 8k people, it isn&amp;rsquo;t too much bigger on paper than other places we looked at, but it feels larger. I&amp;rsquo;d wager a guess that a lot of people drive in from the surrounding areas for work. Bath is right along a river, so there is a good amount of boat related activities. They also have a nice downtown and the people we talked to are very passionate about building community and helping each other out. The schools in the area are all rated 4 out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bath.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bath&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bath2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bath2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also drove south to Boothbay Harbor, which is pretty small with about 1,200 people. The downtown is cute, but a bit touristy, and the day we were there the restaurants had over an hour wait. We aren&amp;rsquo;t sure if this is just due to the troubles all restaurants are having lately, a bad day, or what it&amp;rsquo;s usually like. The land in the area tends to run a bit more expensive, so this is one of those places that if we found the right deal we&amp;rsquo;d consider, but with average prices it&amp;rsquo;s just not affordable for us. The elementary is 6 out of 10, while the high school is 3 out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;boothbay.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;boothbay&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;boothbay2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;boothbay2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;boothbay3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;boothbay3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We briefly visited Thomaston, which has a little under 3k people. It has a tiny downtown, but there&amp;rsquo;s a card store which sells Magic the Gathering, and we spoke with the owner for a while. They are close enough to Rockland that we could easily visit there for more of the downtown experience, and we were very happy to see the town had posted signs bragging about a 92% vaccination rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;thomaston.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;thomaston&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;thomaston2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;thomaston2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maine in general is really nice. They are friendly to solar, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of waterfront due to the shape of the land, and the fresh seafood is hard to turn down. We met so many nice people, but we are a little concerned that we would have a hard time staying active in the winter. Even though coastal Maine has a longer growing season and less harsh winter than places we looked in Vermont and New Hampshire, the culture is that most people hunker down in their houses for the winter rather than go out doing activities like snowshoeing, skiing, etc. Even during the warm season, physical activity seems to rank a little lower here than the other two states. We&amp;rsquo;ve noticed to get good infrastructure to support cycling, walking, running, or other activities, you need a good amount of people in the area who want it. Despite this, Belfast and Bath are ranking really highly on our list of potentials at this point. We have noticed we tend to be biased towards the place we are currently at though, so we&amp;rsquo;ll see how our feelings shift as we move into New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lighthouse.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lighthouse&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lighthouse2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lighthouse2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Central Vermont and New Hampshire</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-08-14/central_vermont_nh.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-08-14/central_vermont_nh.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sorry for the long delay between posts, this long one will cover a lot of ground&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;central-vermont-with-a-little-new-hampshire-jun-26-jul-10&#34;&gt;Central Vermont with a little New Hampshire (Jun 26 - Jul 10)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;vermont_rain.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;vermont_rain&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our first stop in Vermont, we stayed in a little RV park outside of Barre (pronounced berry). We hadn&amp;rsquo;t expected to like Barre, as it has less good ratings on &lt;a href=&#34;http://niche.com&#34;&gt;niche.com&lt;/a&gt; than a lot of the other towns in the area, but I found myself really loving it. Barre has a little of a reputation in the area as &amp;lsquo;Scary Barre&amp;rsquo;, and from what we&amp;rsquo;ve been able to find out, it was much different about 20 years ago from what it is today. The main industry was a granite mine that is either mostly or completely shut down at this point, and drugs were a definite problem. The downtown today is very nice, walkable, has the largest zipper in North America, and Ezri&amp;rsquo;s favorite thing ever: a cat cafe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;barre_zipper.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;barre_zipper&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;barre_cat_cafe2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;barre_cat_cafe2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;barre_cat_cafe3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;barre_cat_cafe3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a hobby store that is up for sale, building and all, that we briefly entertained the idea of buying and taking over. Ultimately, talking to the owner, he gets most of his income from eBay sales rather than from the brick and mortar, since his items are very niche. They have a weekly farmer&amp;rsquo;s market with some really nice people and good amount of fresh produce. We also met a father/daughter duo that are part of the revitalization efforts for Barre, and had a great time talking to them. They of course let us know our search is over, this is the place we need to end up. It&amp;rsquo;s really encouraging meeting people who are so focused on building their community, and it feels like most in Barre are pushing towards that same goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;barre_town.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;barre_town&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the mine was no longer in use, the city bought a good chunk of land from the mine and put in some great mountain bike/hiking trails that weave around the lake that has formed in the bottom of the pit. The discarded rocks in the area bring down the temperature a noticeable amount, which was nice to purposely run by on the hotter days I went running. The schools in the area are a little mixed; Barre Town Elementary has a rating of &lt;sup&gt;7&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;, and Barre City Elementary has a rating of &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;. I found a wooded lot for sale directly next to Barre Town Elementary that would be absolutely perfect if we decided on the area, though I doubt it&amp;rsquo;ll still be there when we&amp;rsquo;ve made our decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;barre_jog.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;barre_jog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;barre_quarry.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;barre_quarry&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;barre_peace_candles.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;barre_peace_candles&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next closest place, and really one of the ones we expected to like the most, is Montpelier. It has a great downtown, and more amenities than Barre (I was going to say it&amp;rsquo;s larger, but turns out it only has a little over 7k people while Barre has over 9k). Montpelier has a population of 25k during the day due to all the people that work there, so that has a lot to do with it. The people in the area are more &amp;lsquo;granola&amp;rsquo; than most other places we&amp;rsquo;ve been so far. There were a few times we weren&amp;rsquo;t sure if someone was wearing ratty clothes because they had to or because they wanted to, and I definitely did not stand out at all with my purple hair. There is a cafe/chocolate shop there that is entirely employee owned, and overall the people we talked to seem very community focused. We also found a great listing for 125 acres up on a hill overlooking a farm for $140k, about 2 miles from downtown. It&amp;rsquo;s cheaper than everything else in the area because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any utilities, and that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what we&amp;rsquo;re looking for. It&amp;rsquo;ll be something we keep an eye on in case we decide on the area. Most of the schools in Montpelier are private, and don&amp;rsquo;t have a rating, but the public schools vary from &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; to &lt;sup&gt;7&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;montpelier_capital.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;montpelier_capital&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;montpelier_church.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;montpelier_church&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;montpelier_downtown.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;montpelier_downtown&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The big city in the area is Burlington, which borders Lake Champlain, and we made it down there for their July 3rd fireworks on the lake. We walked around quite a bit before the fireworks started, and it is a really nice area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;burlington_walk.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;burlington_walk&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;burlinton_boats.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;burlinton_boats&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ezri enjoyed the fireworks, especially after we convinced her to let us put earplugs on her, and she gets excited whenever she hears anyone mention fireworks now. The event was packed, so we also came back on a weekday to check out the city some more without the crowds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;burlington_grass.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;burlington_grass&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;burlington_lake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;burlington_lake&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;burlington_fireworks.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;burlington_fireworks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;burlington_fireworks2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;burlington_fireworks2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They have a museum there, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.echovermont.org/&#34;&gt;ECHO, Leahy Center for Champlain&lt;/a&gt;, that has a lot of hands-on science experiments in addition to your regular museum stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;burlington_science.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;burlington_science&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also found a splash pad while walking around which was perfect with the hot, humid weather. Overall, while the area is nice, it&amp;rsquo;s too busy for us and nice to have as a nearby place to go, but not where we&amp;rsquo;d want to live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;burlington_splash.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;burlington_splash&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove through Waitsfield, which doesn&amp;rsquo;t have as walkable of a downtown, but it does have a church for sale I tried to convince James we need to buy. For some reason he said no, even after I pointed out the stained glass windows!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;waitsfield.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;waitsfield&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We spent the morning of July 4th in Stowe for a parade, which was nice, but the amount of people on the sidelines was about 3x as many as the route could really accommodate, so Ezri was unable to catch any candy past the adults and children that were in front of us. Stowe felt a bit crowded every time we went out there, and property prices in the area are crazy high, so it&amp;rsquo;s not a place we&amp;rsquo;d like to live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;stowe_town.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;stowe_town&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;stowe_parade2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;stowe_parade2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;stowe_parade.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;stowe_parade&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vermont as a state has some things we really like about it. Even the smaller areas have and prioritize recycling, there&amp;rsquo;s a farm stand every few miles, and nearly every restaurant is more &amp;lsquo;farm to table&amp;rsquo; with most of their ingredients coming from local sources. We very rarely saw any trash on the side of the road, where most places we&amp;rsquo;ve been, especially on smaller country roads, there are beer cans and other trash every few feet. Something we didn&amp;rsquo;t notice until it was pointed out to us is that they banned all billboards, and also discourage large chains from being in the area. It&amp;rsquo;s always weird how easily you miss noticing the lack of a nuisance. The tax burden is not as high as New York, but still higher than most other states. We feel like the state is full of people with similar goals and priorities to us, and it&amp;rsquo;s really nice feeling like the whole state is pretty much on the same page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;montpelier_pay_what_you_can.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;montpelier_pay_what_you_can&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During our last couple days at the RV park, we met another couple who are also living on the road full-time with their little girl. Ezri and she had a wonderful time together and we hope that we&amp;rsquo;ll bump back into them at some point. They are documenting their journey on their YouTube channel, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/c/Down2RV/&#34;&gt;Down2RV&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;down2rv.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;down2rv&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;down2rv2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;down2rv2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;central-new-hampshire-with-a-little-vermont-jul-10-jul-24&#34;&gt;Central New Hampshire with a little Vermont (Jul 10 - Jul 24)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;canaan_sunset.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;canaan_sunset&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stayed in Canaan, New Hampshire. The town is quite small, and the RV park itself is almost entirely people who rent spots year-round and have done so for years. It was really interesting seeing the difference in how people act when they have all known each other for so long. They had events every weekend, with a good turnout, and everyone around us was really friendly. Our neighbors behind us offered us free use of their kayaks (we never got the timing right with weather and free time unfortunately), and the lady across from us watched Ezri for us for a few hours one day. We had direct access to a small lake, and one of the neighbors also took us out on his boat to attempt to fish. Since it was last minute, we didn&amp;rsquo;t have any worms, and the fish weren&amp;rsquo;t falling for the lures we had, but it was great to get out on the lake and chat. We were finding mushrooms everywhere, and Ezri was proud to find the biggest one she&amp;rsquo;s seen so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;canaan_nh.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;canaan_nh&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;canaan_mushroom.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;canaan_mushroom&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove out to Littleton, which has a pretty good sized downtown, with a good assortment of stores, but the layout of the roads make it so traffic through the area is forced to drive down the same street. Now that we&amp;rsquo;ve noticed this issue, it&amp;rsquo;s something we really don&amp;rsquo;t like. Having so much traffic makes it much harder to walk the area and makes it feel much less safe for pedestrians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;littleton.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;littleton&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;littleton2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;littleton2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Woodstock Vermont is a town of about 3k people. They have a nice walkable downtown, and the only real downside is the properties in the area are small and pricey. I think this area would end up on our list of &amp;lsquo;if we found a good deal&amp;rsquo;. The schools are really good, with the elementary getting an &lt;sup&gt;8&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;, then one middle school with &lt;sup&gt;8&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; and another with &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;woodstock2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;woodstock2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;woodstock.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;woodstock&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;woodstock3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;woodstock3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Claremont, New Hampshire is a small city of about 13k people. The downtown is a good size, has a delicious Mexican restaurant, but shows the signs of the financial hardship in the area due to the main mill shutting down in the 80s. There are some efforts to revitalize the area; we spoke with a farmer from Claremont who is close in age to us and saw it as an area they want to help bring back up. She is working with the community and was so passionate. It was great to see someone so invested in the area, but we felt ourselves comparing it back to Barre, VT. Barre feels like it is much closer to being the safe, awesome area we want, and Claremont is probably 10-20 years behind it. The schools in the area are also not the greatest, ranging from &lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; to &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;claremont.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;claremont&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tilton, New Hampshire is a town of about 4k people. It has a decently sized downtown, but the assortment of stores aren&amp;rsquo;t as interesting as some we&amp;rsquo;ve seen. Oddly enough, they also have an outlet mall where we grabbed some new shoes and clothes for Ezri. It&amp;rsquo;s a nice town to have nearby, but not an area we would like to live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tilton.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tilton&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lebanon, New Hampshire is a city of about 13k people. There isn&amp;rsquo;t a walkable downtown, but it has a good amount of larger stores. It&amp;rsquo;s not a place we&amp;rsquo;d want to live, but a good one to have nearby for city amenities. It&amp;rsquo;s right next door to Hanover NH (11k) and Norwich Vermont (3.5k), where James and Ezri found the wonderful &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.montshire.org/&#34;&gt;Montshire Museum of Science&lt;/a&gt; and spent a whole afternoon together while I got my hair cut for the first time since Covid. Unfortunately Hanover, Lebanon, and Norwich are surprisingly expensive places to live, possible because of Dartmouth College. These three towns are highly rated as places to raise a family, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think they are quite what we&amp;rsquo;re looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;montshire2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;montshire2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;montshire.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;montshire&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;montshire3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;montshire3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;montshire4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;montshire4&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;montshire5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;montshire5&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next up on our journey is Mid-Coast Maine Jul 24 through Aug 21.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adirondacks and Plattsburgh NY</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-07-07/adirondacks.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-07-07/adirondacks.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ausable_chasm1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ausable_chasm1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our second stop in New York, we stayed in the Ausable (ah-Sable) Chasm Campground in Northeast New York. It was quiet on the weekdays, but had a steady flow of kids on the weekends which Ezri really liked. Our site was right next to the playground, and whenever she heard kids playing out there she wanted to join them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;park.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;park&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ausable_chasm2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ausable_chasm2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we were right next to the Chasm, we made sure to go hike through and take a raft ride. There were other activities offered, but Ezri was under age for those. During the raft ride, we got stuck on a rock. It was such a sudden stop that we were grateful that the people in the front row were able to stay in the boat. After being stuck there long enough to start wondering if we&amp;rsquo;d have to get outside help somehow, with a worker on the side of the river shouting suggestions,  shifting weight around and wiggling a lot, then taking on a fair amount of water on my side, we finally got loose. We felt pretty special that we got half of the people pretty soaked from the waist down, but when we boarded the trolley for the ride back, we found out his last load had had their raft completely flip over. We were really glad to have only been stuck on the rock after hearing that. Neither of these are very common, but they said the river was a little lower than usual, which exposed more rocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_hiking.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_hiking&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezrI_vest.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezrI_vest&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We found a nearby orchard, Rulf&amp;rsquo;s with &amp;lsquo;you pick&amp;rsquo; strawberries. Ezri loved picking her own berries, and I think we found the right balance of getting enough to get the full experience, but not so much that we wasted a lot of them. We saw some families filling 2-3 16qt storage bins completely, and wondered what they planned to do with them all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezr_tractor.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezr_tractor&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_berry.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_berry&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nearby is Keeseville, New York, which is a very small town with not much of a downtown. I found an amazing property there though, an old mill on 2.6 acres, practically on the river. It looks like it would be a ton of work and money, and I have no idea what we&amp;rsquo;d do with 11,000 sqft, but that didn&amp;rsquo;t stop me from getting a few pictures in person and repeatedly asking James if he&amp;rsquo;d fallen in love with the town yet. Spoiler alert, he was not in love. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to find an old building to trick him into buying elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;river.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;river&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mill.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mill&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove up to Plattsburgh, NY a few times during our stay. It has a good, walkable downtown and even a few properties available really close to the downtown. We had a really great experience with the &lt;a href=&#34;http://mauinorth.net/&#34;&gt;local bike shop&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.koffeekat.net/&#34;&gt;coffee shop&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/ACGamingSpace&#34;&gt;card / board gaming shop&lt;/a&gt;, it really feels like the community is getting some great things going. The schools in the area are not the best though, with ratings of &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; to &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;plattsburgh.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;plattsburgh&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;plattsburgh2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;plattsburgh2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A bit longer of a drive away, we went to Lake Placid, NY. It&amp;rsquo;s definitely a tourist destination, and very outdoors focused. The residents all seem to be into sports year-round: skiing, cycling, running, swimming, rowing, hiking, and snowshoeing. We loved seeing so many runners and cyclists out on the roads, and sporting goods stores on every corner. Every person we talked to insisted this is the place to be and they absolutely loved it. The negatives of the area are that there is very little property available in town, what&amp;rsquo;s there is either extremely small or expensive, and it may get a bit crowded at the height of tourist season. The schools in the area are also not the greatest, elementary scored a &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; and middle/high school scored a &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lake_placid.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lake_placid&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lake_placid_dock.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lake_placid_dock&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_run.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_run&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also drove out to Saranac Lake, NY, which is still touristy, but quieter than Lake Placid. They still have a great focus on sports, a good downtown, and some really friendly people that are excited to live there. Properties were still scarce, but there are at least a few that were closer to our size/price range. The schools in the area are slightly better; the elementary schools scored &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; and the high school scored &lt;sup&gt;6&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;saranac_lake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;saranac_lake&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;saranac_lake2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;saranac_lake2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also took a drive through 2 of the major islands on Champlain Lake; Isle La Motte and Grande Isle. Living on an island just sounded so cool, but we quickly realized that while they are nice islands, there are very few amenities and no real running/cycling available. It was still a nice drive, and on the way back we took the ferry, which was a new experience for all of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;island1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;island1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lake_champlain.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lake_champlain&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next up is Vermont, one of the most rural but also progressive states, it&amp;rsquo;ll be an interesting anachronism.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rochester and Finger Lakes Area</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-06-21/fingerlakes.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-06-21/fingerlakes.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;campground-and-erie-canal-trail&#34;&gt;Campground and Erie Canal Trail&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bridge_newark.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bridge_newark&#34; /&gt;We had quite the day driving into Newark, New York (between Rochester and Syracuse). It rained the entire time and we arrived to find our site was relatively new with freshly turned dirt and had turned into a mud puddle. After trying to back the RV in, and spinning our wheels instead, we had to call it good enough once we got the nose of the RV out of the road. We had a very nice neighbor come over with a shovel to help, and James had to unhook the RV, change the truck&amp;rsquo;s position, then re-hook up in order to make the progress he did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;truck_spin.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;truck_spin&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;truck_mud.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;truck_mud&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After waiting a few days for the site to dry out, and the crowds to thin from the long weekend, we were able to swap to a more established site and move over. While having to pack everything back up was a pain, it was definitely worth it to be at a grassy site rather than a mud puddle for the rest of our stay. It rained a few more times and was so much better at the new site. The RV Park has a playground that Ezri wanted to go to constantly, with 3 5 year olds who were staying with their grandparents nearby. She made friends with them and we were able to sit and chat with the adults a few times. They are very familiar with the area and gave us recommendations for what to check out (and where to go for good pies).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rv_pull.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rv_pull&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sunset.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunset&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_umbrella.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_umbrella&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The RV park also has a pool, and Ezri got James to go one day while I worked on stuff around the house. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since she swam, but she took right to it and had a blast. They also have a few ponds on the property, and we were able to watch the tadpoles mature as we were there, with so many batches of them going at once that we could catch one of every stage of development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_frog.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_frog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;rochester-area&#34;&gt;Rochester Area&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;church.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;church&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove out to Irondequoit, a suburb to the North of Rochester, with the intention of spending some time at the water, but seeing a playground caused a change of plans for us instead. The area seemed nice, but has no real downtown and seems to be more just an extension of the city. They have an amusement park, Seabreeze, that looked really interesting. Unfortunately our plans to attend were delayed due to Ezri catching a cold. We waited to buy tickets until she stopped coughing, which was our last day in the area, only to find that they were sold out. If we return to the area we&amp;rsquo;ll definitely try to go, as their website looked to have a good assortment of rides that Ezri could ride on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rides.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rides&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fairport, which is a small town to the East of Rochester on the Erie Canal, had an event &amp;lsquo;Canal Days&amp;rsquo; going on while we were there. They closed the center of town and had booths set up by local businesses and people all along the roads and Canal. It was great to see the turnout, and we got to talk to a lot of nice people about the surrounding areas. Fairport has definitely made an impression on us; they have a great downtown, with the added bonus of the canal in the middle of it (and the bicycle path that runs alongside the canal). The schools in the area vary a little on ratings, ranging from &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; to &lt;sup&gt;8&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;trail_newark.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;trail_newark&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;canal.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;canal&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;canal_days.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;canal_days&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;finger-lakes-towns&#34;&gt;Finger Lakes Towns&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skaneateles (Skinny-atlas) is the only town we looked at on the Syracuse side. We didn&amp;rsquo;t find as many towns of interest in that area and it was a bit more of a drive for us. The town is at the top of a finger lake and is very touristy, so you get the benefits of lots of restaurants and little shops to choose from downtown, but there aren&amp;rsquo;t a lot of larger properties nearby. Those that we could find listings for were more expensive than some of the other areas we looked at. I really liked the vibe, but could also see the area getting a bit annoying with traffic during the peak months. The schools in the area are really good, ranging from &lt;sup&gt;7&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; to &lt;sup&gt;10&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;skan4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;skan4&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;skan_2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;skan_2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;skan.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;skan&#34; /&gt;Canandaigua is a little further South from Rochester, on the tip of one of the finger lakes, and was recommended to us by a few different people. While tourism is definitely part of the industry, it&amp;rsquo;s less busy than Skaneateles. It has a great downtown, and the property prices are a little lower. The county it&amp;rsquo;s in is split close to &lt;sup&gt;50&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;50&lt;/sub&gt; in the last presidential election, so that&amp;rsquo;s a consideration for us, though I think the town itself leans a little more progressive. The schools in the area are decent, but not great. Their elementary school is rated &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;canand.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;canand&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naples was also recommended a few times, we drove out there (on the way is Monica&amp;rsquo;s Pies, if you go to the area you must get some pie or cake there) and found that while it has some nice qualities, the downtown felt too small and it just didn&amp;rsquo;t have enough going on for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;relaxing-fun&#34;&gt;Relaxing Fun&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;museum_window.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;museum_window&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to go to &lt;a href=&#34;https://seabreeze.com/&#34;&gt;Seabreeze&lt;/a&gt; on our last full day here, we instead went to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.museumofplay.org/&#34;&gt;Strong Museum of Play&lt;/a&gt; in Rochester. Ezri really enjoyed a little play house they had with stove burners and an oven that light up so she could pretend cook. We spent a lot of time there. We also lost James for a while to their old arcade games. I think our favorite part of the museum was the butterfly exhibit though. Not only were there butterflies fluttering all over the room, there were some small flightless birds running around that we weren&amp;rsquo;t quite sure were supposed to be there. Looking online I think they were some kind of rail, though I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find an exact match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;museum_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;museum_ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;museum_carousel.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;museum_carousel&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_room.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_room&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;dad_room.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dad_room&#34; /&gt;Oh, James also found his new favorite doll, &amp;lsquo;Little Miss No Name&amp;rsquo;, who horrified children in the 60s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;doll.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;doll&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;doll_close.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;doll_close&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a state level, New York has pretty good abortion and sex education laws (though I think they can always be better). Taxes are a consideration though, New York State has one of the highest overall tax burdens. We know taxes go hand in hand with better education and social programs, but we also need to stay aware of it for our planning and budgeting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centre County Area Pennsylvania</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-06-04/centre.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-06-04/centre.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bridge.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bridge&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the lack of available spaces, we ended up staying in an RV Park in Woodland, PA, near Clearfield, and had to leave on Friday since the upcoming long weekend had the place fully booked for that night. The park has a good playground, a sandbox, a pond with a path circling it, and a few paths cut into the surrounding woods. We had many walks that I intended to be on those wooded paths, but that Ezri quickly insisted should instead become a walk to the playground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_outside.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_outside&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;trail.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;trail&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had 2 major areas we wanted to look at, the first being State College (home of Penn State). We found that the city has the college front and center, so much so that there isn&amp;rsquo;t much else there. We couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a real downtown to go through, and property prices are quite high in the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pennsylvania.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pennsylvania&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nearby is Bellefonte (pronounced bell-font), which we liked a lot more. They have a cute, walkable downtown, and a great park that has bridges, walking trails, and a playground. We enjoyed checking it out and of course spent much of our time at the playground. The people we spoke to were very friendly and said the school system is very good and that the area is &amp;lsquo;very safe&amp;rsquo;. We have found that a mention of an area being safe is a good indicator that someone follows news sources that like to claim all the cities are burning.&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_4&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_5&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_6.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_6&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pennsylvania doesn&amp;rsquo;t get a passing grade on our requirement for state law as a whole (we would have to think this was the best place ever to overlook it). So while we found some nice things, I don&amp;rsquo;t think this will be a contender for our final home. Onward to New York state!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Athens County Ohio</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-05-24/athens.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-05-24/athens.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rainbow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rainbow&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;athens.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;athens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We moved to the Athens, Ohio area on May 1st, kicking off our 2021 season. Due to trouble finding RV parks with openings any closer, we stayed in Coolville, Ohio, about 30 minutes away. Our RV park had a playground with a litter of bunnies living under the merry-go-round, so we got to see some baby bunnies and even gave one of them a little pet. Ezri is so good at being gentle with little creatures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;hair.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;hair&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rabbit.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rabbit&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Athens itself has a decent downtown, but we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to find many family friendly stores. Almost all are aimed at college kids instead, so while the downtown is walkable, the store selection just didn&amp;rsquo;t have much of interest to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we were in the area, Ezri and I drove over the border to Parkersburg, West Virginia while James did some work on the RV. We took a boat to Blennerhassett Island, where a few old buildings and a re-creation of the Blennerhassett mansion is. The original mansion burned down in 1811 and they built the re-creation on the original foundation around 1980. We took the horse drawn carriage ride around the island, but decided against paying for the mansion tour as I didn&amp;rsquo;t think Ezri was up for that much standing around and listening. We did get to see the Putnam Houser house for free; they made a few &amp;lsquo;windows&amp;rsquo; so you could see the construction methods and Ezri had fun looking in them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;boat.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;boat&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mansion.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mansion&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;maple_house.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;maple_house&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ezri got a new bicycle in Athens, which we took to nearby Strouds Run State Park to take advantage of their large parking lots. She&amp;rsquo;s really enjoying having pedals, but we&amp;rsquo;re still working on her pushing hard enough on the pedals to get over small hills or past rocks. She&amp;rsquo;s still too hesitant to try standing up to pedal or putting real force into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rebecca_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rebecca_ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_bike.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_bike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bike.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are always trying to find better ways to decide whether an area is a good candidate for moving to, and since you are affected by state-level laws, I&amp;rsquo;ve started researching the abortion and sex education laws of each state we consider. Ohio is not the best match in that regard, so I don&amp;rsquo;t see it being a contender for where we end up. On May 15th we headed to our next stop, State College, Pennsylvania.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter in Michigan</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-05-17/milan.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-05-17/milan.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;southeast-michigan-nov-14-may-1&#34;&gt;Southeast Michigan (Nov 14 - May 1)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rv_winter.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rv_winter&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey friends! It&amp;rsquo;s been a wee bit longer than I&amp;rsquo;d thought since we last had an update. We had a great time in Milan, Michigan (close to Emily in Saline and near Ann Arbor). Ezri had an exciting joint birthday with her cousin Vera, complete with balloons. She now thinks anytime she has a balloon, we have to get one for Vera too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_vera.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_vera&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;birthday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;birthday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all got together for Christmas as well. While we didn&amp;rsquo;t get to have the usual celebration with all of my siblings and parents, we were very glad to be near my sister Emily and her crew. Ezri got entirely too many presents of course, and we had to rearrange her room to fit it all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;chrismas_tree.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;chrismas_tree&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_lights.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_lights&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_piano.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_piano&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our friends, David and Cindy Parent, and their kids live just about a half hour to the South of Milan in Sylvania Ohio, so after much discussion of safety, we were able to visit with them over the Winter and Spring as well. We used to see them all the time when they lived in Las Vegas, so it was great to get together again. They know the owners of a trampoline park, so they also found out the best, least busy time to go bounce around. Ezri had a blast, James got to play a few great rounds of dodgeball with the older kids, and I discovered just how bad I am at slack-lining. Ezri is anxious to go again, of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_trampoline2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_trampoline2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_trampoline.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_trampoline&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;david.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;david&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went with Emily for a drive up to Frankenmuth, Michigan once the weather got a little less cold. The town was founded by German immigrants, so there is some really interesting architecture and it&amp;rsquo;s a bit of a tourist trap. We didn&amp;rsquo;t make it through too much of the town, as we spent entirely too much time and money in a board game shop we found, but it was definitely a fun trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_franken.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_franken&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went with David and Cindy to the Toledo Zoo. Ezri is always excited to see the fish, and we were really looking forward to the petting zoo area. She was a little scared of the goats and alpacas, but we did get her to touch them a few times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;zoo_aquarium.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;zoo_aquarium&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;zoo_girls.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;zoo_girls&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the weather warmed up a bit more we drove out to Monroe, Michigan on the edge of Lake Erie to play on the beach. We found a tree that had recently been cut down before it fell down, and Ezri had fun hiding in the stump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lake&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;stump.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;stump&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Easter weekend was colder than we&amp;rsquo;d hoped, but we were lucky to find an egg hunt event we could participate in. They did it a little different, most of the eggs were empty and only a few had tickets for prizes. We didn&amp;rsquo;t get any tickets, but we did get a bag of candy for collecting at least one egg, and then sponsors handed out other goodies on the way back to the car. The opportunity for Ezri to interact with adults other than us was great, she likes talking to other adults but her volume is so quiet they almost never hear her, especially through the mask.&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_egg.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_egg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bunny.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bunny&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;easter.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;easter&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Ezri and talking, over the last few months she has decided she is a cat. We&amp;rsquo;re sometimes struggling to get her to use any words other than &amp;lsquo;meow&amp;rsquo;, which makes for hilarious (to me) episodes of her crying meows at James while he tries to figure out what&amp;rsquo;s keeping her from going to sleep at bedtime. Her cat name changes frequently, often just made up names, but she&amp;rsquo;s got a favorite she likes to use: &amp;lsquo;Pompom&amp;rsquo;. We have considered adopting a cat, but with  the size of the RV and Daisy&amp;rsquo;s history of chasing cats, we decided instead to get a hamster, that Ezri has named Mango. Mango loves running around the RV in her hamster ball, and Ezri spends entirely too much time at night watching Mango instead of letting herself go to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_hat.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_hat&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;hamster.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;hamster&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the winter we only got serious snow twice, but we made sure to enjoy it when we got it. Spending the winter here was a bit of test to see if we can handle it after so many years in the desert, and I think this was a more mild winter than normal, but overall we are feeling a-ok with living in an area that gets cold and snowy. I did have a bit of what I suspect to be Seasonal Affective Disorder, but a little vitamin D seemed to clear it right up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_snow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_snow&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The timing barely worked, but before leaving the area, we were able to get both doses of our COVID vaccines. The first we just had some arm soreness, but the second dose hit me pretty hard with chills and a fever of 102. James was just a little tired, so it worked out that he was able to keep Ezri happy while I recovered. Still well worth the safety, obviously. While we were waiting for the vaccines, James also had to get a little dental surgery for his front teeth, luckily the timing worked out for that and we were able to get all the appointments taken care of before leaving the area. It&amp;rsquo;s certainly nice to have a friend in the industry (Cindy) to help keep us taken care of!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;teeth.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;teeth&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On May 1st we left out to the first stop for this year, Athens, Ohio. We&amp;rsquo;re moving every two weeks this year, and unlike past moves, we&amp;rsquo;ve had to schedule all the way out to October because of the increased park demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a reminder, you can check out our current travel plans at &lt;a href=&#34;https://colefamily.page/plan/&#34;&gt;https://colefamily.page/plan/&lt;/a&gt; and see the travel map at &lt;a href=&#34;https://colefamily.page/map/&#34;&gt;https://colefamily.page/map/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween in Champaign-Urbana Illinois, but Winter is Coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-12-21/champaign.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-12-21/champaign.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;champaign-urbana-illinois-oct-30-nov-14&#34;&gt;Champaign-Urbana, Illinois (Oct 30 - Nov 14)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-kite-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-kite-2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Champaign Illinois is a larger town of 88k people. It&amp;rsquo;s home to the University of Illinois, so it has a lot of the same cultural, restaurant, and cycling amenities that come with it. We arrived the day before Halloween, and found a drive-thru trunk or treat the same night. After waiting in line for over an hour, we made it through and Ezri was very excited to get candy and talk to the people handing it out. On Halloween day we found an event at the local library where Ezri got to pick out a book in addition to a treat bag, then we figured we&amp;rsquo;d hit one more drive thru that started in the afternoon. That turned out to be a less good idea, we got in line at the exact time the event was supposed to start, and after waiting in line for 2.5 hours (.5 hours after it was supposed to end), we reached the start to be told they were out of candy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;facepaint.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;facepaint&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;dressed-up1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dressed-up1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;dressed-up2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dressed-up2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The park we stayed at has a pond that we enjoyed walking around, and 3 cats who like to follow whoever is near one end of the pond. If Ezri had her way, we&amp;rsquo;d have spent almost all our time out there petting cats. We are slowly getting used to it, but there are so many more bugs around than there were in Vegas. There were a lot of Asian Lady-beetles in the area, and they kept letting themselves into the house. Ezri loves having them as pets, so we caught them in jars for her, then got an actual bug box and got nearly 15 at once. I have to admit, we then didn&amp;rsquo;t have any food for them and forgot to let them loose outside in time. Luckily they are an invasive species, so I guess we can say we did our part. We&amp;rsquo;ll continue trying to remember to let her friends go before it&amp;rsquo;s too late, but that&amp;rsquo;s usually met with tears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pond.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pond&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-pond.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-pond&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-is-doggy.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-is-doggy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While in the area, we discovered a high-school friend of our friend Paul Grayson lived nearby, so we met up with them and their kids at the playground for some masked, mostly distanced socializing. They filled us in on some of the amenities. The school system is ranked highly, and has full immersion Spanish available at two of the private schools. There are restaurants of all kinds, though with the restrictions we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to try more than a few while in town. It&amp;rsquo;s clear they really enjoy the area, and near the University definitely has a lot of the stuff we are looking for, though land prices that close are also too high.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-park.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-park&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-park1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-park1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the reasons we chose to visit this area is that James recently got a new Step-mom, Peggy, and Champaign is within a few hours of her hometown where she and his dad are living. We met halfway between, at an outdoor zoo, and had lunch at a Mexican restaurant afterwards. The zoo had a wide assortment of animals, including a &amp;lsquo;petting zoo&amp;rsquo; area where we could feed them some pellet food through the fence. Ezri liked feeding the goats, and we got close to getting the deer to eat, but there were 2 pushy cows that kept nosing all the other animals away. The cows were also the drooliest eaters, so Ezri quickly decided she didn&amp;rsquo;t like feeding them. We had to divide and conquer, with James distracting the cows with snacks so Ezri and I could feed the goats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-mom-zoo.jpg.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-mom-zoo.jpg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-dad-zoo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-dad-zoo&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-deer.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-deer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-goat.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-goat&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;grandpa-ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;grandpa-ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we were driving back, we stopped at a gas station with some concrete spheres to separate the sidewalk from the parking lot, and Ezri insisted it was time for a photo shoot. We also happened upon a damaged windmill, which was a crazy sight, with just how big those things are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-ball.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-ball&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;broken-windmill.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;broken-windmill&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;winter-destination-milan-michigan-nov-14-spring-2021&#34;&gt;Winter Destination: Milan, Michigan (Nov 14 - Spring 2021 ?)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mi-park-swing.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mi-park-swing&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We left on November 14th, and have settled into Milan, Michigan for the winter. My sister, Emily, lives nearby and we spent Thanksgiving with her family. It&amp;rsquo;s been wonderful being near them, though Ezri has made it clear the real reason she wants to visit so often and never leave is their 3 cats. Her cousin, Vera, has a birthday near hers, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be celebrating with a joint birthday party for them this weekend. Ezri is old enough now that she understands the concept of surprises and has asked that her cake be a surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll share more in our next blog post!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mi-tree.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mi-tree&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesy Jokes in Madison Wisconsin</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-11-11/madison.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-11-11/madison.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;deforest-madison-suburbs&#34;&gt;DeForest (Madison Suburbs)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_mexican.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_mexican&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DeForest is a suburb of about 9k people North of Madison, Wisconsin. We were eager to check out the Madison area as it is one of the few places in the US that has a car crash testing site, which is the type of work my sister, Emily does. If we decided to live in the area, there&amp;rsquo;s a chance we could eventually convince her to join us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The area itself has a good amount of trails and I loved the proximity to Target and Jo-Ann&amp;rsquo;s (I&amp;rsquo;ve been sewing a lot more this season). The trade-off, unfortunately, is that the land and house prices are quite a bit higher, and outside of what our ideal would be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_jacket_2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_jacket_2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_jacket.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_jacket&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The RV Park we stayed at had a playground on-site, so we spent a ton of time there with Ezri. She also enjoyed playing in the leaves since fall was in full effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_leaves.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_leaves&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;madison&#34;&gt;Madison&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;madison_1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;madison_1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove into Madison proper, which has a population of 260k, but didn&amp;rsquo;t spend a ton of time since most things are shut down and we had a bit of a cold snap during our visit. We were excited to see some really good street art, but overall the city center felt very crowded and busy, with a lot of traffic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;wisconsin-dells&#34;&gt;Wisconsin Dells&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sunset.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunset&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we talked to people in the area, a few recommended we check out Wisconsin Dells, so we drove up there. The city itself has less than 3k residents, but is primarily a tourist destination. We were surprised by how many water-parks were there, one after the other, indoor, outdoor, and with amusement park rides as well. We also passed a ropes course that looked like a ton of fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The original draw for tourists to Wis Dells (the short name we&amp;rsquo;ve seen used several places) is the Wisconsin river that cuts through the center. The day we drove out there was pretty chilly, but we were lucky to find a boat with 2 decks, one enclosed with a heater and one open air. The boat tour took us up the river to 2 different stops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;river.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;river&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first stop was Witches Gulch, named due to the strange rock/whirlpool formations and beliefs of the local Natives that it was haunted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;hiking.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;hiking&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second stop was at a rock formation made famous when a photographer caught a picture of their son jumping across a gap onto a precarious looking rock tower. They had a trained dog jump across, and we tried to time our pictures to catch the mid-air moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rocks.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rocks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the boat ride, we grabbed dinner at a restaurant with a model train track running through it. We assumed it was just there for decoration, until we saw it go by loaded with drinks. They use the train to deliver each table&amp;rsquo;s drinks, appetizers, and small entres.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;train1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;train1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;train2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;train2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;halloween-prep&#34;&gt;Halloween Prep&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halloween is just around the corner the day after we arrive in Champaign, Illinois, so I spent time working on a new skeleton costume for Ezri, she&amp;rsquo;s been really into anatomy this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;costume_1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;costume_1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;costume_2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;costume_2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;costume_3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;costume_3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James and Ezri carved 2 pumpkins this year, Ezri is very aware of emotions now and had a lot of fun planning the face each would have. Ezri wanted the first pumpkin to be spookier, she&amp;rsquo;s really been getting into the spirit with all the Halloween decorations at the store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin_0.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin_0&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin_3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin_3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin_2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin_2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin_1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin_1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s all for this update, until next time!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
