<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cole Family</title>
    <link>https://www.colefamily.page/</link>
    <description>  Cole Family</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.colefamily.page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bumpy Road to Pacific City and Cascade Locks</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-04-11/bumpy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-04-11/bumpy.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Apologies, this is a little late, it was written on April 3rd; the next post about Joseph, OR will be forthcoming.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our last few weeks in Fall City didn&amp;rsquo;t go as we had planned, as we got a call in the middle of the night that James&amp;rsquo;s step-mom, Kim, had passed away. Luckily James&amp;rsquo;s work has paid bereavement leave and my work can be flexible, allowing us to fly out to Tennessee to support his dad. The funeral was beautiful, and we were able to catch up with friends and family we didn&amp;rsquo;t see during our Christmas trip out there. We were all shocked by her passing, and will miss her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tn_bug.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tn_bug&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James has transitioned within Red Hat to a new role of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redhat.com/en/blog/being-technical-account-manager-tam-day-life&#34;&gt;Technical Account Manager&lt;/a&gt; which is mostly remote and will only require travel a few times a quarter. We are very excited for the increased time we&amp;rsquo;ll spend together, and it&amp;rsquo;s nice to not have to worry about proximity to an airport when planning our stops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The drive from Fall City to Pacific City Oregon was relatively uneventful. Some of the mountain roads had sunken grade and other damage that made for a bumpy ride. The RV Park we stayed in was really nice, and the stay was free for us since we have a membership to Thousand Trails. The membership cost just a little more than a 2 week stay, and gives us free stays in member RV parks as long as it&amp;rsquo;s been at least a week since we last were in one and we don&amp;rsquo;t stay longer than 14 days. It&amp;rsquo;ll be a while until we&amp;rsquo;re at a location with another Thousand Trails park, but we&amp;rsquo;ve already more than made up for the price of membership by staying 2 weeks free in Fall City, then 2 weeks free in Pacific City.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;family_pacificcity.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;family_pacificcity&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pacific City is directly on the coast, and has some great local restaurants. We were able to walk directly from the RV Park to the beach. Ezri loved playing in the sand, even though it was a bit chilly and windy each time we went. When we first arrived, we opted to eat out more than normal, and I am so glad we did, since we barely beat the spread of COVID-19 and subsequent closing of dine-in areas. The people we talked to were friendly, and we discovered most of the houses in Pacific City are vacation rentals. Not sure how that would impact the overall culture, but it seemed a little too tourist heavy to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pacificcity_rock.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pacificcity_rock&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The RV Park we stayed at is unfortunately in an area with minimal cell signal. We were unable to make/receive phone calls from our site; text messages were hit and miss. Luckily our AT&amp;amp;T connection we use for wifi was slightly stronger, and we had enough Internet to stay connected via hangouts and other tools, but to get any work done we had to either go to the Family Center or a nearby coffee shop. The Family Center has a pool table, ping pong, a few arcade games, and a room of toys for younger kids, as well as several tables and chairs, so I took Ezri there almost every day so she could play while I worked for an hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bunnies.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bunnies&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;mommy_baby.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mommy_baby&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few miles south of Pacific City is Lincoln City, we spent the day out there shopping in their outlet mall for new clothes for Ezri, since she&amp;rsquo;d pretty much outgrown all of her 2T stuff. The town seems more kid-friendly, one store had a table covered in sand and toys with a sign encouraging kids to play, and a coffee shop there had games out on every table. It was hard to get her to go with us into the clothing stores since all she wanted to do was play marbles again! Overall, I really enjoyed the vibe and availability of stores in Lincoln City.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;North of Pacific City, we went up to Netarts and Oceanside. Both had some lovely restaurants with fresh seafood. Oceanside&amp;rsquo;s beach sometimes has geodes, so we walked along it looking for them. We found a few tiny ones, along with shells, and Ezri had fun digging in all of the rocks and sand. We also drove up a bit further to Cape Mears to the shortest, stubbiest lighthouse we&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lighthouse.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lighthouse&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With stricter directives that are practically a shelter in place order coming to Oregon, we spent the latter half of our stay mostly within the RV Park. They locked all of the buildings, so no more Family Center, but I got furloughed right around the same time and no longer had the need to work. James still needed to get work done, so he would drive the truck to the Family Center or the coffee shop, connect to their Wi-Fi, and work from within the truck. Not the most ideal situation, but it worked. Since we were inside so much, we decided it was the perfect time to potty train. Using the 3 day method right before a car trip wasn&amp;rsquo;t ideal, but we went for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;coffee_shop.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;coffee_shop&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, James&amp;rsquo;s brother, Joseph, ended up in the hospital while we were in Pacific City; hours from the nearest airport. We discussed having James fly out to see him, but were worried about potentially spreading COVID-19, as well as taking time off from a new job right after taking bereavement leave. James was at least able to use up his Southwest miles to fly out his mom and dad, but they were unable to get into the hospital when they arrived. Due to virus concerns, they shut it down to visitors. After a few days, Joseph was discharged and seems to be pretty much back to normal, which was a big relief.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our drive to the next stop, Cascade Locks, Oregon, was only about 3 hours. Since Ezri was so new to potty training, we planned a few stops. The first one was harder to get to than we&amp;rsquo;d thought, so we took a chance and skipped it. At the 2 hour mark we stopped at a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s for lunch and tried to have a potty break, to find that she is not OK using restaurant bathrooms. Afterwards, we drove the rest of the way to the RV Park, and then she used her little potty in the back of my car. I was shocked she made it about 3.5 hours without any accidents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;cascadelocks.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;cascadelocks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve been in Cascade Locks for about a week and a half, and will be leaving on Saturday. Technically the RV park we are in is closed, but the owners aren&amp;rsquo;t kicking out people like us who aren&amp;rsquo;t vacationers. The RV Park is right next to the railroad tracks, and while the trains were exciting initially, they run most often during the night and have woken us all up several times. We&amp;rsquo;re looking forward to getting a quiet night&amp;rsquo;s sleep at the next place. We are disappointed we haven&amp;rsquo;t really had an opportunity to check out the area or culture much, we can see some amazing cycling/walking/jogging trails by the highway and the maps show many trail-heads, but the weather has been a bit rainy and cold whenever we have the time to go, and the trail-heads look like they are closed anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;cascadelocks2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;cascadelocks2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next stop is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nytimes.com/2017/07/20/travel/wallowa-valley-mountains-joseph-oregon-culture.html&#34;&gt;Joseph, Oregon&lt;/a&gt;. We originally planned to stay 2 weeks there, but are discussing whether we should stay until the socialization limitations are lifted, as the whole point of this journey is to get a feel for different places, and we aren&amp;rsquo;t able to do that without interacting with people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Since we updated this post late, here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of part of the drive to Joseph, Oregon:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;joseph_drive.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;joseph_drive&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall City Washington and Busy Busy Holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-02-16/holidays.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-02-16/holidays.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey friends, been meaning to write an update for a while, so many things have built up to update you on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re staying in an RV Resort near Fall City, a town of about 2,000 people. We are about 30 minutes from Issaquah, and 20 minutes from Andrew, Jason, and Ben (my brothers). This spot is more private than some of the others we&amp;rsquo;ve stayed at, and we accidentally got a site that is right in the middle of where a lot of the employees are staying. That has been a benefit as we have gotten to know them well over this time, we have consistent neighbors, and one of our neighbors even volunteered to watch Daisy for us when we were out of town for Christmas. The weather here has been very wet, this is one of the most rainy Januarys they&amp;rsquo;ve had in several years. Such a huge difference from Las Vegas weather, and it&amp;rsquo;s nice to see green things, but I&amp;rsquo;m a bit sick of the mud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;snow-rv.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Snowy RV&#34; /&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;flood.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Flooded Road&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We settled in just in time for Thanksgiving. It was wonderful to be able to spend it with family and friends after being on the road for a few months. The lack of friends and family nearby has been the hardest part of RV living.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ezri turned 2 on December 13th, we had a little party in the rec center at the RV Park, and Andrew, Jason, Ben, and their families were able to join us. Ezri loves playing with her cousins, and though she didn&amp;rsquo;t really care for the cake, she did enjoy the pizza and presents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-bday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ezri&#39;s Birthday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Debbie, Steve, and Todd were able to come out for an early Christmas, and Ben hosted all of us at his roommate&amp;rsquo;s house. It was wonderful seeing everyone. Emily and her family weren&amp;rsquo;t able to come out, but she sent a giant order of fancy breads and pastries that were delicious. Ezri and Nathan loved playing in the shredded paper they came packed in, and loved being &amp;lsquo;monsters&amp;rsquo; by covering themselves head to toe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-cousins.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ezri and Cousins&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next week, we flew out to Tennessee to see James&amp;rsquo;s family. It had been about 8 years since we last went out there, so the trip was long overdue. When so much time has passed, it&amp;rsquo;s always hard to reconcile just how much people have changed with what we have in our heads. James&amp;rsquo;s dad and stepmom are helping out a relative with a daughter that is one, so Ezri got to play with lots of toys while we were there, and she enjoyed having baby playtime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-tn.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ezri in Tennessee&#34; /&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;ezri-fish.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ezri at Aquarium&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In mid-January, Ezri and I made a 7 hour (each way) drive to Grants Pass, Oregon to see my Grandma and Grandpa, and were joined by Emily (my sister) and her 2 youngest. We also got to visit with my cousin who lives in the area and has 2 daughters near Ezri&amp;rsquo;s age. It was a great visit, Ezri had so much fun with her cousins (and second cousins), and I loved the chance to catch up with Emily in person. It was also nice to find out that we can drive for so long without any major meltdowns. On both drives Ezri dumped her bag of snacks all over herself and the car, but Cheeto stains and having to vacuum were definitely not the worst that could have happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-gran.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ness Family&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My license and car registration were up for renewal around my birthday, and the DMV wouldn&amp;rsquo;t let me renew online, so after much discussion, we decided I&amp;rsquo;d fly out for a quick 24 hour trip to Las Vegas to get it taken care of. After 2.5 hours sitting at the DMV, my license is good for another 8 years, and my car registration is good until March 2021. I was a little worried that Ezri would give James a hard time in my absence, since she and I rarely spend any time apart. They had a grand time, and I think she hardly noticed I was gone. James took her to an event at Home Depot where they introduce kids to tools, and she made a cute heart decoration. We&amp;rsquo;ll be seeking out these events in the future for sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-heart.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ezri Heart&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Issaquah has a gym here with a daycare, but unique to them is that next door is a sports center with bounce houses and inflatable slides. They have an agreement that the gym daycare kids can come over and bounce, so Ezri loves going to the gym. We have been making it about 3 days a week on average, and I&amp;rsquo;m feeling like I&amp;rsquo;m making decent progress in getting back in shape. I will be sad to leave the gym behind when we move on to the next place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of moving on, we have &lt;a href=&#34;./map&#34;&gt;updated the map with the tentative route for 2020&lt;/a&gt;! Our goal is to reach Ann Arbor, Michigan just after Halloween, and spend the winter there with Emily. Our reservation here is up on March 7th, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be heading South to Pacific City, Oregon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./map&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;route.png&#34; alt=&#34;route&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walla Walla Washington</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-12-10/wallawalla.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-12-10/wallawalla.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bluevalleyrv.com/&#34;&gt;Blue Valley RV Park&lt;/a&gt; we stayed at in Walla Walla had a great paved path that connected to the park, then went alongside a golf-course, some fields, and a few neighborhoods. With adding a few loops around a track that wasn&amp;rsquo;t far off the path, I was able to run a full 10k. Unfortunately, I also discovered a recurring leg pain I thought I had rested away was not actually gone yet. Doing some research into proper gait and posture when running with a stroller, and hopefully I can get that one solved soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The town itself was really great; The downtown area was very walkable, and there were vineyards and wine tasting rooms everywhere. We found a wonderful restaraunt called &lt;a href=&#34;https://maplecountercafe.com/&#34;&gt;Maple Counter Cafe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;breakfast1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;breakfast1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;breakfast2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;breakfast2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Walla Walla didn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of indoor kids activities due to its size, but they did have a Children&amp;rsquo;s Museum. Ezri had a blast there; they had a water table with sand and toys so you could make dams, redirect the water, and generally just make a mess. They also had a climbing wall with a slide at the top that she had a lot of fun on, and a giant tube with a fan underneath it that you could put scarves and ribbons under: the air would catch them, spin them up, and out the top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sandbox2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sandbox2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sandbox1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sandbox1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were very lucky that we were in town when a local business was celebrating a big anniversary. They threw a party at the local fairgrounds, and Ezri and I got to go. (James was in Las Vegas, more about that next.) At first, the sheer number of people and noise level was a lot for her to handle, and she needed to be held while covering her ears. After about 20 minutes though, she relaxed a little. I was surprised when Ezri wanted to go into a bounce house with the bigger kids, but figured worst case I&amp;rsquo;d go in there and get her if it was too much. She LOVED it. Once I even had to tell some older girls who thought she was too young to stop holding her hands and let her jump. They also had a huge inflatable slide that Ezri wanted to try. I thought the climb up might be too much, but sure enough, she went for it and had a ball. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to catch a picture of her at the top, but you can see her right after she got to the bottom of the slide. She was the last one out of the bounce house. She didn&amp;rsquo;t want to leave and I had to go in and get her so they could shut it down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;slide.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;slide&#34; /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our house is finally, completely, sold!&lt;/strong&gt; James had to spend a weekend in Las Vegas packing up all of the furniture we had left for staging and moving it into storage. We loved that house, but it&amp;rsquo;s great to no longer be paying for the mortgage and utilities on top of our expenses on the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;storage.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;storage&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Walla Walla was very foggy, at least half of the days we were there had fog, with most of those being bad enough for there to be weather advisories. I can confidently say I do not enjoy being in fog for more than a day at a time, it starts to feel a little claustrophobic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;park3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;park3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;parknight2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;parknight2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, my car started acting up about halfway through our stay. When it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t turn over one morning, I assumed a dead battery, but testing at the AutoZone didn&amp;rsquo;t uncover any obvious issue other than the battery being low. Testing the alternator revealed a too high ripple so we thought just replacing the battery wouldn&amp;rsquo;t solve our problem. I bought a battery jump starter, and used that for most of the time we were there, but the last few days the battery was so bad that the electronics weren&amp;rsquo;t acting right, headlights would turn off randomly, so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t safe to drive anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My car is still covered under warranty, but the nearest dealership was over 200 miles away in Tacoma, Washington. Luckily Mini roadside assistance policy is a free tow to the nearest dealership. I had to remind the worker I talked to of that before they agreed to cover it, but ultimately won out and got them to pay for the tow. Ezri and I rode in the truck to Issaquah with James, which was both good and bad. It was nice being all together, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize just how much comfort I get from following behind the RV and being able to see there are no issues with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once we got the car to the dealership, they declared all that was wrong was a bad battery, and covered that under the warranty. I&amp;rsquo;m still sceptical, but luckily we are close by so if this battery dies too, at least it won&amp;rsquo;t be as big of an ordeal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mini.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mini&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate that we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to spend a little more time together as a family in Walla Walla because of the Las Vegas trip, but we wanted to get over the mountains before the ice and snow hit &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wsdot.com/traffic/passes/snoqualmie/&#34;&gt;Snoqualmie Pass&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;drive1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;drive1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;drive2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;drive2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We arrived in Fall City, Washington near Issaquah on November 23rd. We just paid for a long-term stay until March 7th since James will be working in the area for the next couple of months at least, and it should be a nice place to wait out Winter. We&amp;rsquo;ll have another post about our last few weeks here at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rvonthego.com/washington/tall-chief-rv-camping-resort/&#34;&gt;Tall Chief RV Resort&lt;/a&gt; in the next few days, stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tallchief1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tallchief1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;James Note: Sorry for so few pictures of Walla Walla without fog, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t always dreary looking, we were just busy!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Idaho Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-11-07/homedale.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-11-07/homedale.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Boise Idaho area was beautiful, we visited at the perfect time to see the leaves changing color. On our drive we saw several fields of various crops, including hops, corn, alfalfa, apples, and pomegranates. While it got a little chilly at night, most days it was warm enough that we could bundle up and spend time outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;snakeriver.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;snakeriver&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We decided to stay at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://snakeriverrv.com/&#34;&gt;Snake River Resort RV&lt;/a&gt; park outside of Boise in Homedale Idaho. It is on the river, with our morning view consisting of ducks and fog rolling on the river each morning. They have a little walking trail that takes you around the neighboring alfalfa field. Ezri&amp;rsquo;s favorite part of the walk on it was finding a grocery bag that had gotten stuck on the fence, freeing it, and filling it with rocks she found along the trail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Boise, we visited a Children&amp;rsquo;s Museum, which was much more of a toy collection than a museum, so right up Ezri&amp;rsquo;s alley. She loved playing on a horse that you press down on the &amp;lsquo;stirrups&amp;rsquo; to move forward, and had to spend time hugging all of the stuffed animals in their play vet&amp;rsquo;s office. She also enjoyed the Magna Tiles, especially destroying any creation I put together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;horse.gif&#34; alt=&#34;horse&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also went to &lt;a href=&#34;https://warhawkairmuseum.org/&#34;&gt;The Warhawk Air Museum&lt;/a&gt; in Nampa, which turned out to be a little too hands-off for Ezri (note from James: &lt;em&gt;definitely check it out if you like restored warbirds, especially the P40, my favorite. They had an incredible amount of historical information.&lt;/em&gt;). They did have 2 sealed domes with gloves attached that are like the ones sometimes used in space to perform experiments when the chemicals involved can be dangerous to the people or equipment. They had a Duplo set inside one, and a Lego set inside the other. Ezri enjoyed trying to grab the pieces with the giant gloves, but also kept trying to get the pieces out by pulling them through the glove holes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James and Ezri created a Jack-O-Lantern together on the Saturday before Halloween, and we did a trunk or treat on the Sunday.
&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin-collage.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin-collage&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Halloween, they have a trick or treat event where businesses throughout their downtown area opt in to handing out candy. It worked out great for us because we didn&amp;rsquo;t have to intrude on a neighborhood we weren&amp;rsquo;t really a part of. She was pretty shy for most of it, and only spoke to one adult who was dressed up as a butterfly. She definitely was understanding the concept though, and would hold out her bucket for each place we stopped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mirror.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mirror&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;costume.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;costume&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ezri is almost through eating all of her candy, her favorites have been lollipops by far, but she also liked gummy bears and skittles a lot. I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to when she finishes her candy; I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to keep up with all the sticky hand prints she&amp;rsquo;s been putting on the furniture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sucker.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sucker&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We moved onward to Walla Walla Washington on November 2nd, and so far it&amp;rsquo;s been great as well, we&amp;rsquo;ll have more updates soon! (Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to checkout the &lt;a href=&#34;./map/&#34;&gt;Route Map&lt;/a&gt; link for current location and planned stops)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;route.png&#34; alt=&#34;route&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada Wrap-Up - Great Basin and Elko NV</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-10-26/great-basin-elko.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-10-26/great-basin-elko.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, James here!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our final week in Ely, we drove out to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nps.gov/grba/&#34;&gt;Great Basin National Park&lt;/a&gt; where we got to see Wheeler Peak, the second highest mountain in Nevada.  This is a wonderful, out of the way park that we really should&amp;rsquo;ve spent a few more days exploring. Wheeler Peak is 13,065 ft high, and you can drive to over 10,000 ft in your car - It really hits home just how high you are when you realize that if you were in an airliner, you could go to the bathroom at this height on a normal flight :-)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;wheeler-peak.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;wheeler-peak&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After visiting the park, including the Peak and doing the Lehman Cave tour, we stopped by an amazing little gourmet restaurant called &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.stargazernevada.com/&#34;&gt;Kerouac&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt; started by a couple from New York who started it in 2017. There&amp;rsquo;s not much else on Highway 50, that&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s known as &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;The Loneliest Road in America&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;. You might go for dozens of miles without seeing anyone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also stopped by the &lt;a href=&#34;http://parks.nv.gov/parks/ward-charcoal-ovens&#34;&gt;Ward Charcoal Ovens&lt;/a&gt; only used for three years during the 1870s silver boom. Ezri loved playing with the echoes in the ovens, and the surrounding country-side was beautiful and made for a great little day hike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-oven.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-oven&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;echo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;echo&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We wrapped up Ely by Rebecca and Ezri learning to bake together - She loves to be involved in any activity we&amp;rsquo;re doing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-stirring.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-stirring&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-rebecca-stirring.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-rebecca-stirring&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;short-stay-in-elko-nv&#34;&gt;Short stay in Elko, NV&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now, from Rebecca (since James had to travel to Orlando for work):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ely was a great transition for Elko, since Ezri got used to the sound of trains and was no longer scared of them. All of the RV parks are close to the train tracks, and trains were a normal occurrence for us. Elko was a short stay, only a week. Unfortunately, since we drove on Saturday, and were setting up the RV Sunday, James didn&amp;rsquo;t get much of a chance to see the town before we headed out again the following Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ezri and I went to the Chamber of Commerce, which is run from an old fort and has historic wagons and buildings on the lot. The only thing Ezri was really into there was the rocking chairs on their front porch. Next door to that is the Northeastern Nevada Museum, which has some examples of local rocks and gems, and historic clothing and daily living items. They also have a wing with over 200 taxidermy animals from all over the world, many of which I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen before. &lt;img src=&#34;rocking-chair.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rocking-chair&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got our first glimpse of real fall, and a neighbor loaned us their rake so we could make a pile to play in. Ezri loved playing in the leaves, and helping remake the pile each time it spread out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;leaves-play.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;leaves-play&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;leaves.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;leaves&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;grass.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;grass&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The drive to Boise was rather eventful for us. Due to 2 RV parks near Boise having the same name, and a bit of assumption on our part that we were navigating to the same place, a quick stop for gas caused me to take an entirely different route than James, that was an hour longer. By the time we realized the issue, doubling back would cause the same amount of time difference, so I corrected the destination and continued on. We both experienced snow, hail, rain, and extremely high winds on our drive. At one point, my heart rate was high for long enough that FitBit automatically logged an aerobic activity for me, lasting 23 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;onward-to-boise-id&#34;&gt;Onward to Boise, ID&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like Rebecca said, our drive to Boise was pretty interesting, so here is a photo of my snowy drive, at least from before it really started sleeting and before the wind blew so hard and I was too white-knuckled holding the RV on the road to take many pictures!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;snowy.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;snowy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Aboard to Ely Nevada!</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-10-08/ely.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-10-08/ely.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ely_train.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re getting close to the end of our stay in Ely, and it&amp;rsquo;s been a really great time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a train museum here, with a steam train and a diesel train you can buy tickets for. We rode the steam train, and Ezri had so much fun talking about the train and imitating the choo choo. The ride itself takes 90 minutes, with historical information peppered throughout. We were surprised to learn that in the early 1900s, Ely was the biggest town in Nevada, and had the tallest building (the Nevada Hotel, a whopping 6 stories high). The amount of ore that the trains have hauled during the 1900s was staggering as well, how much was needed for a small amount of copper was very surprising. Ezri has been getting better and better about conquering her fears; it was awesome seeing Ezri go from mildly terrified when we first arrived to absolutely excited and wanting to get closer to the train.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also went up to Garnet Hill, and found a few super tiny garnets. We&amp;rsquo;re planning on going up to Great Basin National Park this week, and James is trying to convince me we can find space to store a few fishing poles in the RV so we can go fishing at Cave Lake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a bit colder than we anticipated, but true to high desert, the temperature varies greatly from the night to day. We have gotten a good system of using the propane heater at night while it&amp;rsquo;s below 30, and opening the windows during the day to keep from going above 80 inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wifi has been slow at best, which I suppose we should have expected (James said he totally saw this one coming). It&amp;rsquo;s done wonders for our streaming habits, and I felt nostalgic today trying to download a file, and watching the estimated time go from 2 days to 3 days, to 5 days, to a download failure. We ordered a Netgear Nighthawk N1 LTE Modem with external antennas, and a few sim cards from Google Fi to get our own network going, a cost we had hoped to hold off until after the house sells, but a necessity for staying sane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We knew we were going to a remote area, with much fewer amenities, but it really didn&amp;rsquo;t sink in until we saw this shirt in the gift shop. The nearest Walmart will be at our next stop, Elko, which we will be driving to on Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;walmart.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cole’s Law Brakers - Living on the Road</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-09-21/first-post.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-09-21/first-post.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rv.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rv&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After much thought, research, and planning, we’re almost ready to hit the road! Our first target is Issaquah, Washington (near the Seattle area) where the client James is working with is located. We’re taking our time getting there, going up through Nevada, to a corner of Idaho, over into Oregon, and then into Washington. We don’t have exact dates for all of the locations yet, but we have locked in our reservation in Ely, Nevada for October 1st through 12th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rebecca has quit her job and will be trying to keep Ezri out of trouble full time with a little freelance work during naps, while James will continue to work for RedHat and fly back and forth to his client in Issaquah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see our planned stops, potential places to live, and current location on the map at any time. We’ll be updating at least every time we change locations. If you know of cool places we should check out along the way, definitely let us know!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
