<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cole Family</title>
    <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/</link>
    <description>  Cole Family</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.colefamily.page/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Adirondacks and Plattsburgh NY</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-07-07/adirondacks.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-07-07/adirondacks.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ausable_chasm1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ausable_chasm1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our second stop in New York, we stayed in the Ausable (ah-Sable) Chasm Campground in Northeast New York. It was quiet on the weekdays, but had a steady flow of kids on the weekends which Ezri really liked. Our site was right next to the playground, and whenever she heard kids playing out there she wanted to join them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;park.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;park&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ausable_chasm2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ausable_chasm2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we were right next to the Chasm, we made sure to go hike through and take a raft ride. There were other activities offered, but Ezri was under age for those. During the raft ride, we got stuck on a rock. It was such a sudden stop that we were grateful that the people in the front row were able to stay in the boat. After being stuck there long enough to start wondering if we&amp;rsquo;d have to get outside help somehow, with a worker on the side of the river shouting suggestions,  shifting weight around and wiggling a lot, then taking on a fair amount of water on my side, we finally got loose. We felt pretty special that we got half of the people pretty soaked from the waist down, but when we boarded the trolley for the ride back, we found out his last load had had their raft completely flip over. We were really glad to have only been stuck on the rock after hearing that. Neither of these are very common, but they said the river was a little lower than usual, which exposed more rocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_hiking.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_hiking&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezrI_vest.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezrI_vest&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We found a nearby orchard, Rulf&amp;rsquo;s with &amp;lsquo;you pick&amp;rsquo; strawberries. Ezri loved picking her own berries, and I think we found the right balance of getting enough to get the full experience, but not so much that we wasted a lot of them. We saw some families filling 2-3 16qt storage bins completely, and wondered what they planned to do with them all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezr_tractor.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezr_tractor&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_berry.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_berry&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nearby is Keeseville, New York, which is a very small town with not much of a downtown. I found an amazing property there though, an old mill on 2.6 acres, practically on the river. It looks like it would be a ton of work and money, and I have no idea what we&amp;rsquo;d do with 11,000 sqft, but that didn&amp;rsquo;t stop me from getting a few pictures in person and repeatedly asking James if he&amp;rsquo;d fallen in love with the town yet. Spoiler alert, he was not in love. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to find an old building to trick him into buying elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;river.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;river&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mill.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mill&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove up to Plattsburgh, NY a few times during our stay. It has a good, walkable downtown and even a few properties available really close to the downtown. We had a really great experience with the &lt;a href=&#34;http://mauinorth.net/&#34;&gt;local bike shop&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.koffeekat.net/&#34;&gt;coffee shop&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/ACGamingSpace&#34;&gt;card / board gaming shop&lt;/a&gt;, it really feels like the community is getting some great things going. The schools in the area are not the best though, with ratings of &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; to &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;plattsburgh.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;plattsburgh&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;plattsburgh2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;plattsburgh2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A bit longer of a drive away, we went to Lake Placid, NY. It&amp;rsquo;s definitely a tourist destination, and very outdoors focused. The residents all seem to be into sports year-round: skiing, cycling, running, swimming, rowing, hiking, and snowshoeing. We loved seeing so many runners and cyclists out on the roads, and sporting goods stores on every corner. Every person we talked to insisted this is the place to be and they absolutely loved it. The negatives of the area are that there is very little property available in town, what&amp;rsquo;s there is either extremely small or expensive, and it may get a bit crowded at the height of tourist season. The schools in the area are also not the greatest, elementary scored a &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; and middle/high school scored a &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lake_placid.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lake_placid&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lake_placid_dock.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lake_placid_dock&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_run.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_run&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also drove out to Saranac Lake, NY, which is still touristy, but quieter than Lake Placid. They still have a great focus on sports, a good downtown, and some really friendly people that are excited to live there. Properties were still scarce, but there are at least a few that were closer to our size/price range. The schools in the area are slightly better; the elementary schools scored &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; and the high school scored &lt;sup&gt;6&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;saranac_lake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;saranac_lake&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;saranac_lake2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;saranac_lake2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also took a drive through 2 of the major islands on Champlain Lake; Isle La Motte and Grande Isle. Living on an island just sounded so cool, but we quickly realized that while they are nice islands, there are very few amenities and no real running/cycling available. It was still a nice drive, and on the way back we took the ferry, which was a new experience for all of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;island1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;island1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lake_champlain.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lake_champlain&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next up is Vermont, one of the most rural but also progressive states, it&amp;rsquo;ll be an interesting anachronism.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rochester and Finger Lakes Area</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-06-21/fingerlakes.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-06-21/fingerlakes.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;campground-and-erie-canal-trail&#34;&gt;Campground and Erie Canal Trail&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bridge_newark.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bridge_newark&#34; /&gt;We had quite the day driving into Newark, New York (between Rochester and Syracuse). It rained the entire time and we arrived to find our site was relatively new with freshly turned dirt and had turned into a mud puddle. After trying to back the RV in, and spinning our wheels instead, we had to call it good enough once we got the nose of the RV out of the road. We had a very nice neighbor come over with a shovel to help, and James had to unhook the RV, change the truck&amp;rsquo;s position, then re-hook up in order to make the progress he did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;truck_spin.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;truck_spin&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;truck_mud.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;truck_mud&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After waiting a few days for the site to dry out, and the crowds to thin from the long weekend, we were able to swap to a more established site and move over. While having to pack everything back up was a pain, it was definitely worth it to be at a grassy site rather than a mud puddle for the rest of our stay. It rained a few more times and was so much better at the new site. The RV Park has a playground that Ezri wanted to go to constantly, with 3 5 year olds who were staying with their grandparents nearby. She made friends with them and we were able to sit and chat with the adults a few times. They are very familiar with the area and gave us recommendations for what to check out (and where to go for good pies).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rv_pull.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rv_pull&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sunset.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunset&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_umbrella.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_umbrella&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The RV park also has a pool, and Ezri got James to go one day while I worked on stuff around the house. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since she swam, but she took right to it and had a blast. They also have a few ponds on the property, and we were able to watch the tadpoles mature as we were there, with so many batches of them going at once that we could catch one of every stage of development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_frog.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_frog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;rochester-area&#34;&gt;Rochester Area&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;church.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;church&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove out to Irondequoit, a suburb to the North of Rochester, with the intention of spending some time at the water, but seeing a playground caused a change of plans for us instead. The area seemed nice, but has no real downtown and seems to be more just an extension of the city. They have an amusement park, Seabreeze, that looked really interesting. Unfortunately our plans to attend were delayed due to Ezri catching a cold. We waited to buy tickets until she stopped coughing, which was our last day in the area, only to find that they were sold out. If we return to the area we&amp;rsquo;ll definitely try to go, as their website looked to have a good assortment of rides that Ezri could ride on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rides.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rides&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fairport, which is a small town to the East of Rochester on the Erie Canal, had an event &amp;lsquo;Canal Days&amp;rsquo; going on while we were there. They closed the center of town and had booths set up by local businesses and people all along the roads and Canal. It was great to see the turnout, and we got to talk to a lot of nice people about the surrounding areas. Fairport has definitely made an impression on us; they have a great downtown, with the added bonus of the canal in the middle of it (and the bicycle path that runs alongside the canal). The schools in the area vary a little on ratings, ranging from &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; to &lt;sup&gt;8&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;trail_newark.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;trail_newark&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;canal.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;canal&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;canal_days.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;canal_days&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;finger-lakes-towns&#34;&gt;Finger Lakes Towns&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skaneateles (Skinny-atlas) is the only town we looked at on the Syracuse side. We didn&amp;rsquo;t find as many towns of interest in that area and it was a bit more of a drive for us. The town is at the top of a finger lake and is very touristy, so you get the benefits of lots of restaurants and little shops to choose from downtown, but there aren&amp;rsquo;t a lot of larger properties nearby. Those that we could find listings for were more expensive than some of the other areas we looked at. I really liked the vibe, but could also see the area getting a bit annoying with traffic during the peak months. The schools in the area are really good, ranging from &lt;sup&gt;7&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; to &lt;sup&gt;10&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;skan4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;skan4&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;skan_2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;skan_2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;skan.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;skan&#34; /&gt;Canandaigua is a little further South from Rochester, on the tip of one of the finger lakes, and was recommended to us by a few different people. While tourism is definitely part of the industry, it&amp;rsquo;s less busy than Skaneateles. It has a great downtown, and the property prices are a little lower. The county it&amp;rsquo;s in is split close to &lt;sup&gt;50&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;50&lt;/sub&gt; in the last presidential election, so that&amp;rsquo;s a consideration for us, though I think the town itself leans a little more progressive. The schools in the area are decent, but not great. Their elementary school is rated &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;canand.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;canand&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naples was also recommended a few times, we drove out there (on the way is Monica&amp;rsquo;s Pies, if you go to the area you must get some pie or cake there) and found that while it has some nice qualities, the downtown felt too small and it just didn&amp;rsquo;t have enough going on for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;relaxing-fun&#34;&gt;Relaxing Fun&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;museum_window.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;museum_window&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to go to &lt;a href=&#34;https://seabreeze.com/&#34;&gt;Seabreeze&lt;/a&gt; on our last full day here, we instead went to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.museumofplay.org/&#34;&gt;Strong Museum of Play&lt;/a&gt; in Rochester. Ezri really enjoyed a little play house they had with stove burners and an oven that light up so she could pretend cook. We spent a lot of time there. We also lost James for a while to their old arcade games. I think our favorite part of the museum was the butterfly exhibit though. Not only were there butterflies fluttering all over the room, there were some small flightless birds running around that we weren&amp;rsquo;t quite sure were supposed to be there. Looking online I think they were some kind of rail, though I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find an exact match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;museum_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;museum_ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;museum_carousel.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;museum_carousel&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_room.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_room&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;dad_room.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dad_room&#34; /&gt;Oh, James also found his new favorite doll, &amp;lsquo;Little Miss No Name&amp;rsquo;, who horrified children in the 60s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;doll.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;doll&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;doll_close.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;doll_close&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a state level, New York has pretty good abortion and sex education laws (though I think they can always be better). Taxes are a consideration though, New York State has one of the highest overall tax burdens. We know taxes go hand in hand with better education and social programs, but we also need to stay aware of it for our planning and budgeting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centre County Area Pennsylvania</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-06-04/centre.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-06-04/centre.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bridge.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bridge&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the lack of available spaces, we ended up staying in an RV Park in Woodland, PA, near Clearfield, and had to leave on Friday since the upcoming long weekend had the place fully booked for that night. The park has a good playground, a sandbox, a pond with a path circling it, and a few paths cut into the surrounding woods. We had many walks that I intended to be on those wooded paths, but that Ezri quickly insisted should instead become a walk to the playground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_outside.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_outside&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;trail.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;trail&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had 2 major areas we wanted to look at, the first being State College (home of Penn State). We found that the city has the college front and center, so much so that there isn&amp;rsquo;t much else there. We couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a real downtown to go through, and property prices are quite high in the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pennsylvania.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pennsylvania&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nearby is Bellefonte (pronounced bell-font), which we liked a lot more. They have a cute, walkable downtown, and a great park that has bridges, walking trails, and a playground. We enjoyed checking it out and of course spent much of our time at the playground. The people we spoke to were very friendly and said the school system is very good and that the area is &amp;lsquo;very safe&amp;rsquo;. We have found that a mention of an area being safe is a good indicator that someone follows news sources that like to claim all the cities are burning.&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_4&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_5&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bellefonte_6.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bellefonte_6&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pennsylvania doesn&amp;rsquo;t get a passing grade on our requirement for state law as a whole (we would have to think this was the best place ever to overlook it). So while we found some nice things, I don&amp;rsquo;t think this will be a contender for our final home. Onward to New York state!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Athens County Ohio</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-05-24/athens.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-05-24/athens.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rainbow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rainbow&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;athens.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;athens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We moved to the Athens, Ohio area on May 1st, kicking off our 2021 season. Due to trouble finding RV parks with openings any closer, we stayed in Coolville, Ohio, about 30 minutes away. Our RV park had a playground with a litter of bunnies living under the merry-go-round, so we got to see some baby bunnies and even gave one of them a little pet. Ezri is so good at being gentle with little creatures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;hair.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;hair&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rabbit.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rabbit&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Athens itself has a decent downtown, but we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to find many family friendly stores. Almost all are aimed at college kids instead, so while the downtown is walkable, the store selection just didn&amp;rsquo;t have much of interest to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we were in the area, Ezri and I drove over the border to Parkersburg, West Virginia while James did some work on the RV. We took a boat to Blennerhassett Island, where a few old buildings and a re-creation of the Blennerhassett mansion is. The original mansion burned down in 1811 and they built the re-creation on the original foundation around 1980. We took the horse drawn carriage ride around the island, but decided against paying for the mansion tour as I didn&amp;rsquo;t think Ezri was up for that much standing around and listening. We did get to see the Putnam Houser house for free; they made a few &amp;lsquo;windows&amp;rsquo; so you could see the construction methods and Ezri had fun looking in them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;boat.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;boat&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mansion.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mansion&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;maple_house.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;maple_house&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ezri got a new bicycle in Athens, which we took to nearby Strouds Run State Park to take advantage of their large parking lots. She&amp;rsquo;s really enjoying having pedals, but we&amp;rsquo;re still working on her pushing hard enough on the pedals to get over small hills or past rocks. She&amp;rsquo;s still too hesitant to try standing up to pedal or putting real force into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rebecca_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rebecca_ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_bike.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_bike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bike.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are always trying to find better ways to decide whether an area is a good candidate for moving to, and since you are affected by state-level laws, I&amp;rsquo;ve started researching the abortion and sex education laws of each state we consider. Ohio is not the best match in that regard, so I don&amp;rsquo;t see it being a contender for where we end up. On May 15th we headed to our next stop, State College, Pennsylvania.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter in Michigan</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-05-17/milan.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2021-05-17/milan.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;southeast-michigan-nov-14-may-1&#34;&gt;Southeast Michigan (Nov 14 - May 1)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rv_winter.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rv_winter&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey friends! It&amp;rsquo;s been a wee bit longer than I&amp;rsquo;d thought since we last had an update. We had a great time in Milan, Michigan (close to Emily in Saline and near Ann Arbor). Ezri had an exciting joint birthday with her cousin Vera, complete with balloons. She now thinks anytime she has a balloon, we have to get one for Vera too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_vera.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_vera&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;birthday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;birthday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all got together for Christmas as well. While we didn&amp;rsquo;t get to have the usual celebration with all of my siblings and parents, we were very glad to be near my sister Emily and her crew. Ezri got entirely too many presents of course, and we had to rearrange her room to fit it all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;chrismas_tree.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;chrismas_tree&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_lights.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_lights&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_piano.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_piano&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our friends, David and Cindy Parent, and their kids live just about a half hour to the South of Milan in Sylvania Ohio, so after much discussion of safety, we were able to visit with them over the Winter and Spring as well. We used to see them all the time when they lived in Las Vegas, so it was great to get together again. They know the owners of a trampoline park, so they also found out the best, least busy time to go bounce around. Ezri had a blast, James got to play a few great rounds of dodgeball with the older kids, and I discovered just how bad I am at slack-lining. Ezri is anxious to go again, of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_trampoline2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_trampoline2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_trampoline.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_trampoline&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;david.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;david&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went with Emily for a drive up to Frankenmuth, Michigan once the weather got a little less cold. The town was founded by German immigrants, so there is some really interesting architecture and it&amp;rsquo;s a bit of a tourist trap. We didn&amp;rsquo;t make it through too much of the town, as we spent entirely too much time and money in a board game shop we found, but it was definitely a fun trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_franken.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_franken&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went with David and Cindy to the Toledo Zoo. Ezri is always excited to see the fish, and we were really looking forward to the petting zoo area. She was a little scared of the goats and alpacas, but we did get her to touch them a few times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;zoo_aquarium.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;zoo_aquarium&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;zoo_girls.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;zoo_girls&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the weather warmed up a bit more we drove out to Monroe, Michigan on the edge of Lake Erie to play on the beach. We found a tree that had recently been cut down before it fell down, and Ezri had fun hiding in the stump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lake&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;stump.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;stump&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Easter weekend was colder than we&amp;rsquo;d hoped, but we were lucky to find an egg hunt event we could participate in. They did it a little different, most of the eggs were empty and only a few had tickets for prizes. We didn&amp;rsquo;t get any tickets, but we did get a bag of candy for collecting at least one egg, and then sponsors handed out other goodies on the way back to the car. The opportunity for Ezri to interact with adults other than us was great, she likes talking to other adults but her volume is so quiet they almost never hear her, especially through the mask.&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_egg.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_egg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bunny.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bunny&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;easter.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;easter&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Ezri and talking, over the last few months she has decided she is a cat. We&amp;rsquo;re sometimes struggling to get her to use any words other than &amp;lsquo;meow&amp;rsquo;, which makes for hilarious (to me) episodes of her crying meows at James while he tries to figure out what&amp;rsquo;s keeping her from going to sleep at bedtime. Her cat name changes frequently, often just made up names, but she&amp;rsquo;s got a favorite she likes to use: &amp;lsquo;Pompom&amp;rsquo;. We have considered adopting a cat, but with  the size of the RV and Daisy&amp;rsquo;s history of chasing cats, we decided instead to get a hamster, that Ezri has named Mango. Mango loves running around the RV in her hamster ball, and Ezri spends entirely too much time at night watching Mango instead of letting herself go to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_hat.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_hat&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;hamster.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;hamster&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the winter we only got serious snow twice, but we made sure to enjoy it when we got it. Spending the winter here was a bit of test to see if we can handle it after so many years in the desert, and I think this was a more mild winter than normal, but overall we are feeling a-ok with living in an area that gets cold and snowy. I did have a bit of what I suspect to be Seasonal Affective Disorder, but a little vitamin D seemed to clear it right up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_snow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_snow&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The timing barely worked, but before leaving the area, we were able to get both doses of our COVID vaccines. The first we just had some arm soreness, but the second dose hit me pretty hard with chills and a fever of 102. James was just a little tired, so it worked out that he was able to keep Ezri happy while I recovered. Still well worth the safety, obviously. While we were waiting for the vaccines, James also had to get a little dental surgery for his front teeth, luckily the timing worked out for that and we were able to get all the appointments taken care of before leaving the area. It&amp;rsquo;s certainly nice to have a friend in the industry (Cindy) to help keep us taken care of!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;teeth.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;teeth&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On May 1st we left out to the first stop for this year, Athens, Ohio. We&amp;rsquo;re moving every two weeks this year, and unlike past moves, we&amp;rsquo;ve had to schedule all the way out to October because of the increased park demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a reminder, you can check out our current travel plans at &lt;a href=&#34;https://colefamily.page/plan/&#34;&gt;https://colefamily.page/plan/&lt;/a&gt; and see the travel map at &lt;a href=&#34;https://colefamily.page/map/&#34;&gt;https://colefamily.page/map/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween in Champaign-Urbana Illinois, but Winter is Coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-12-21/champaign.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-12-21/champaign.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;champaign-urbana-illinois-oct-30-nov-14&#34;&gt;Champaign-Urbana, Illinois (Oct 30 - Nov 14)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-kite-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-kite-2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Champaign Illinois is a larger town of 88k people. It&amp;rsquo;s home to the University of Illinois, so it has a lot of the same cultural, restaurant, and cycling amenities that come with it. We arrived the day before Halloween, and found a drive-thru trunk or treat the same night. After waiting in line for over an hour, we made it through and Ezri was very excited to get candy and talk to the people handing it out. On Halloween day we found an event at the local library where Ezri got to pick out a book in addition to a treat bag, then we figured we&amp;rsquo;d hit one more drive thru that started in the afternoon. That turned out to be a less good idea, we got in line at the exact time the event was supposed to start, and after waiting in line for 2.5 hours (.5 hours after it was supposed to end), we reached the start to be told they were out of candy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;facepaint.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;facepaint&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;dressed-up1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dressed-up1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;dressed-up2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dressed-up2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The park we stayed at has a pond that we enjoyed walking around, and 3 cats who like to follow whoever is near one end of the pond. If Ezri had her way, we&amp;rsquo;d have spent almost all our time out there petting cats. We are slowly getting used to it, but there are so many more bugs around than there were in Vegas. There were a lot of Asian Lady-beetles in the area, and they kept letting themselves into the house. Ezri loves having them as pets, so we caught them in jars for her, then got an actual bug box and got nearly 15 at once. I have to admit, we then didn&amp;rsquo;t have any food for them and forgot to let them loose outside in time. Luckily they are an invasive species, so I guess we can say we did our part. We&amp;rsquo;ll continue trying to remember to let her friends go before it&amp;rsquo;s too late, but that&amp;rsquo;s usually met with tears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pond.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pond&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-pond.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-pond&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-is-doggy.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-is-doggy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While in the area, we discovered a high-school friend of our friend Paul Grayson lived nearby, so we met up with them and their kids at the playground for some masked, mostly distanced socializing. They filled us in on some of the amenities. The school system is ranked highly, and has full immersion Spanish available at two of the private schools. There are restaurants of all kinds, though with the restrictions we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to try more than a few while in town. It&amp;rsquo;s clear they really enjoy the area, and near the University definitely has a lot of the stuff we are looking for, though land prices that close are also too high.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-park.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-park&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-park1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-park1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the reasons we chose to visit this area is that James recently got a new Step-mom, Peggy, and Champaign is within a few hours of her hometown where she and his dad are living. We met halfway between, at an outdoor zoo, and had lunch at a Mexican restaurant afterwards. The zoo had a wide assortment of animals, including a &amp;lsquo;petting zoo&amp;rsquo; area where we could feed them some pellet food through the fence. Ezri liked feeding the goats, and we got close to getting the deer to eat, but there were 2 pushy cows that kept nosing all the other animals away. The cows were also the drooliest eaters, so Ezri quickly decided she didn&amp;rsquo;t like feeding them. We had to divide and conquer, with James distracting the cows with snacks so Ezri and I could feed the goats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-mom-zoo.jpg.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-mom-zoo.jpg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-dad-zoo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-dad-zoo&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-deer.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-deer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-goat.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-goat&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;grandpa-ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;grandpa-ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we were driving back, we stopped at a gas station with some concrete spheres to separate the sidewalk from the parking lot, and Ezri insisted it was time for a photo shoot. We also happened upon a damaged windmill, which was a crazy sight, with just how big those things are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-ball.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-ball&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;broken-windmill.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;broken-windmill&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;winter-destination-milan-michigan-nov-14-spring-2021&#34;&gt;Winter Destination: Milan, Michigan (Nov 14 - Spring 2021 ?)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mi-park-swing.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mi-park-swing&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We left on November 14th, and have settled into Milan, Michigan for the winter. My sister, Emily, lives nearby and we spent Thanksgiving with her family. It&amp;rsquo;s been wonderful being near them, though Ezri has made it clear the real reason she wants to visit so often and never leave is their 3 cats. Her cousin, Vera, has a birthday near hers, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be celebrating with a joint birthday party for them this weekend. Ezri is old enough now that she understands the concept of surprises and has asked that her cake be a surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll share more in our next blog post!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mi-tree.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mi-tree&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesy Jokes in Madison Wisconsin</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-11-11/madison.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-11-11/madison.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;deforest-madison-suburbs&#34;&gt;DeForest (Madison Suburbs)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_mexican.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_mexican&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DeForest is a suburb of about 9k people North of Madison, Wisconsin. We were eager to check out the Madison area as it is one of the few places in the US that has a car crash testing site, which is the type of work my sister, Emily does. If we decided to live in the area, there&amp;rsquo;s a chance we could eventually convince her to join us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The area itself has a good amount of trails and I loved the proximity to Target and Jo-Ann&amp;rsquo;s (I&amp;rsquo;ve been sewing a lot more this season). The trade-off, unfortunately, is that the land and house prices are quite a bit higher, and outside of what our ideal would be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_jacket_2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_jacket_2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_jacket.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_jacket&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The RV Park we stayed at had a playground on-site, so we spent a ton of time there with Ezri. She also enjoyed playing in the leaves since fall was in full effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_leaves.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_leaves&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;madison&#34;&gt;Madison&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;madison_1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;madison_1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We drove into Madison proper, which has a population of 260k, but didn&amp;rsquo;t spend a ton of time since most things are shut down and we had a bit of a cold snap during our visit. We were excited to see some really good street art, but overall the city center felt very crowded and busy, with a lot of traffic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;wisconsin-dells&#34;&gt;Wisconsin Dells&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sunset.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunset&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we talked to people in the area, a few recommended we check out Wisconsin Dells, so we drove up there. The city itself has less than 3k residents, but is primarily a tourist destination. We were surprised by how many water-parks were there, one after the other, indoor, outdoor, and with amusement park rides as well. We also passed a ropes course that looked like a ton of fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The original draw for tourists to Wis Dells (the short name we&amp;rsquo;ve seen used several places) is the Wisconsin river that cuts through the center. The day we drove out there was pretty chilly, but we were lucky to find a boat with 2 decks, one enclosed with a heater and one open air. The boat tour took us up the river to 2 different stops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;river.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;river&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first stop was Witches Gulch, named due to the strange rock/whirlpool formations and beliefs of the local Natives that it was haunted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;hiking.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;hiking&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second stop was at a rock formation made famous when a photographer caught a picture of their son jumping across a gap onto a precarious looking rock tower. They had a trained dog jump across, and we tried to time our pictures to catch the mid-air moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rocks.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rocks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the boat ride, we grabbed dinner at a restaurant with a model train track running through it. We assumed it was just there for decoration, until we saw it go by loaded with drinks. They use the train to deliver each table&amp;rsquo;s drinks, appetizers, and small entrées.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;train1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;train1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;train2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;train2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;halloween-prep&#34;&gt;Halloween Prep&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halloween is just around the corner the day after we arrive in Champaign, Illinois, so I spent time working on a new skeleton costume for Ezri, she&amp;rsquo;s been really into anatomy this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;costume_1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;costume_1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;costume_2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;costume_2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;costume_3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;costume_3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James and Ezri carved 2 pumpkins this year, Ezri is very aware of emotions now and had a lot of fun planning the face each would have. Ezri wanted the first pumpkin to be spookier, she&amp;rsquo;s really been getting into the spirit with all the Halloween decorations at the store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin_0.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin_0&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin_3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin_3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin_2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin_2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin_1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin_1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s all for this update, until next time!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wind Powered Excitement in Pella and Knoxville Iowa</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-10-29/knoxville_pella.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-10-29/knoxville_pella.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;knoxville-iowa&#34;&gt;Knoxville, Iowa&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knoxville is a pretty small town (about 7k people), and doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot going on other than the sprint car raceway and museum they have. We stayed about a mile from a nice park, so Ezri had us walking to the playground frequently. If she had her way, we&amp;rsquo;d do nothing else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_rainbow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_rainbow&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing we noticed about this area is that the towns all seem to have a central square with city hall, and their main street surrounds the square. They had a farmer&amp;rsquo;s market 2x a week in the square, and we went once; there were only a few stalls, but we bought a bunch of green peppers as we&amp;rsquo;ve all been on a pepper salad kick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weather has been really nice, so I got a decent amount of running in, and we also tried to walk whenever we could. During one of our walks we came across the creepiest lion statue we&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen in front of a veterinary office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;james_lion.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;james_lion&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During one of my runs, I noticed a bat in the middle of the sidewalk. I stopped, called James, and discussed what to do, we decided to see if it was still there on my way back. Sure enough, poor guy was still there, and refused to move from the sidewalk. I tried gently prodding with a stick but it just showed its teeth rather than move. I finished my run, then we doubled back with the car, a box, and some rags to gather it up. We contacted a rescue and were instructed to try putting it on a tree, so we picked one on the edge of the RV park that we could check back on, and tried it. We were shocked by how quickly the bat went from unmoving to climbing happily up the tree. Turns out if they fly during the day they get easily disoriented and scared, and are unable to take off from the ground, so they just kind of hunker down and wait until night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bat.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bat&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A little ways north is Cordova Park, which has an observation tower you can climb for $.50 a person. We paid our quarters, went in, and noticed a bunch of ladybugs all over the tower. Then came the biting gnats, and as we got up a little higher, the yellow jackets. I guess we didn&amp;rsquo;t pick the best time of year, but we only spent a few seconds at the top before hurrying back down to avoid all the flying pests. I was a little disappointed as the views would have been really nice had we had the time to enjoy them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tower.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tower&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tower_inside.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tower_inside&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;pella-iowa&#34;&gt;Pella, Iowa&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pella_downtown.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pella_downtown&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pella_fountain.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pella_fountain&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we had been able to find an RV park in Pella, I think that&amp;rsquo;s where we would have stayed, the town has more potential for us long term than Knoxville. Pella is a very unique town of about 10k people, settled by a religious group from the Netherlands in 1847. They have held onto their Dutch heritage, with many buildings in the center of town built with Dutch architecture, a yearly tulip festival, a canal in the middle of the street, and a working windmill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pella_windmill.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pella_windmill&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We took a tour of the windmill and surrounding museum, which included:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A massive mini train village of buildings found in the Netherlands&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tiny_town.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tiny_town&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several preserved historical buildings from the early days of the town&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;water_wheel.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;water_wheel&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;village.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;village&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some giant shoes that Ezri loved trying on&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;shoes.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;shoes&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pella may be a familiar name to you, the main company in town is Pella windows, with some of the towns income coming from tourism as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also enjoyed having Poffertjes (tiny pancakes covered in powdered sugar) and Stroopwafels at the local chain coffee shop, DutchFix. When telling locals of our travels and the reason for them, the most common response we got is &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rsquo;ll love it here, the schools are great and there are a lot of churches!&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yankton, South Dakota (and South Yankton, Nebraska)</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-10-17/yankton.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-10-17/yankton.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bridge1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bridge1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yankton spans across the state line, though most of the city is in South Dakota. The RV park we stayed in is right next to a 2 layer former rail/car bridge that is now strictly for pedestrians. We were about a mile from the downtown via the bridge, so we used it quite a bit. Underneath the bridge, they also have a few miles of rough trail that Ezri and I ran on. It was enjoyable, and she thought it was extra fun with all of the bumps and turns, but I ran face first into several spiderwebs, one with the spider still in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;trail.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;trail&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bridge2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bridge2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also had easy access to the Missouri River, with nice sandy banks that we attempted to make sand castles on, but ultimately couldn&amp;rsquo;t get the moisture level correct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_water.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_water&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Yankton downtown is nice, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t have as much going on as some of the other places we&amp;rsquo;ve been. There&amp;rsquo;s not a lot of foot traffic or the type of businesses you window shop at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While in Yankton, we officially became South Dakotans! We got new licenses, but were surprised to find out that they don&amp;rsquo;t have a DMV; licenses and registration are handled by 2 completely different departments. We should have registered our vehicles while in the Black Hills, so James had to make a flight from our current stop to take care of the truck and RV, while I&amp;rsquo;ll make a flight later on to get the car switched over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;james_plane.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;james_plane&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason we switched residency mostly comes down to the registration, in Nevada we were paying about 3x as much, and they required a Nevada smog check each year, that we can&amp;rsquo;t get since we aren&amp;rsquo;t near there. In South Dakota we&amp;rsquo;ll be able to renew each year without worrying about smog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;vermillion-sd&#34;&gt;Vermillion, SD&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;castle.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;castle&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vermillion is about a half hour from Yankton, so we also checked out the area there. Overall, we liked Vermillion a little better, there are a few more interesting things and it&amp;rsquo;s a bit more progressive, probably due to the fact that it&amp;rsquo;s a college town. They aren&amp;rsquo;t allowed to mandate masks due to state rules, but they have a &amp;lsquo;masks expected&amp;rsquo; policy. We also saw several rainbow signs in business windows showing support for LGBTQ rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mask.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mask&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rights.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rights&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vermillion&amp;rsquo;s main street has the only breakfast place we could find that is open on Sunday (between both Vermillion and Yankton) and is very walkable with a few more browsable shops than Yankton had. They also have a gorgeous old church that looks like a castle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also on the main street we found a robotics club for kids that Ezri wanted to join immediately. She&amp;rsquo;s a bit too young, but it&amp;rsquo;s nice to see STEM related things like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;robotics.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;robotics&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a hard time finding any fabric stores in the area with anything besides quilting fabric, so we made the hour&amp;rsquo;s drive to Hawarden, Iowa to a fabric outlet. It was interesting seeing this tiny town with hardly anything going on with such a large fabric store. I overheard other customers and it seems many drive hours to get there. I got some &amp;lsquo;water damaged&amp;rsquo; denim for 1.99 a yard and corduroy for 2.99 a yard that should keep me busy for a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;in-weave.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;in-weave&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;fabric.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;fabric&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Black Hills of South Dakota (Lead / Deadwood / Rapid City)</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-09-28/black_hills.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-09-28/black_hills.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;blackhills_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;blackhills_ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we stayed mostly in Deadwood, the whole area needs to be taken into account, so I&amp;rsquo;ve broken up some of this by city. This area has a lot of history so I&amp;rsquo;ll include some as it&amp;rsquo;s really necessary to see why we chose to visit and why it is now our top spot on our ranking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;spearfish&#34;&gt;Spearfish&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stayed a few days in Spearfish, due to the site in Deadwood not being available yet. We were able to find an RV park with a walking path that connected to a larger paved bike path. Ezri and I did a couple runs and walks through there and she found a love for trying to imitate the buzzing insects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;spearfish_trail.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;spearfish_trail&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This RV park also has daily ice cream socials, $3 a person for all you can eat, and we were thrilled to find it was outdoors and properly distanced. It was a really great way to meet and chat with our fellow RVers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;spearfish_koa.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;spearfish_koa&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spearfish is a medium small town, with about 10k people, and large enough to have a decent selection of restaurants, chain grocery stores, and a Wal-Mart. It&amp;rsquo;s only about a 25 minute drive from Deadwood, so our next hop was a short one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;spearfish_goodday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;spearfish_goodday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;spearfish_hatchery.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;spearfish_hatchery&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the cheap tires that came with the RV decided to develop bubbles already, so we also had to upgrade them while at our next stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;cheap_tires.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;cheap_tires&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;deadwood&#34;&gt;Deadwood&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_mansion.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_mansion&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stayed in an RV park nestled into a gulch for the rest of the 3 weeks we were in the area, and practically on the George S. Mickelson Trail, 108.8 miles of dirt trail that follows a former railroad. Perfect for running, walking, cycling, and open to snowmobiles in the winter, this is one of the reasons we wanted to check out the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_rv_park.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_rv_park&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwod_trail.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwod_trail&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deadwood is a small town of 1300, and has a famous history as an old west town, with a cemetery near the top of a mountain that has the graves of Wild Bill Hickok, Calamity Jane, and Seth Bullock. Around that area is also a hiking trail that Ezri and I took; though we accidentally went off trail and nearly doubled the distance, we had a lot of fun and there were some really great views.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_ezri_sitting.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_ezri_sitting&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the old West history, Deadwood&amp;rsquo;s main income source is tourism, and they have a great downtown with a lot of activities (though some are shut down due to covid). Every Thursday night is family night at the open air stage, and almost every day they have reenacted shootouts on main street every 2 hours for the tourists. There are also casinos with single deck blackjack, cheap prime rib buffets, and James says it really reminds him of old Vegas, back when he first got there. There&amp;rsquo;s also a coffee shop/glass blowing studio with some gorgeous pieces. They normally have glass blowing classes too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_glass_one.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_glass_one&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_glass_two.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_glass_two&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The area is very mountainous, so most of the houses are built multi-storied, with small footprints and tiny yards. They also frequently will have stairs leading from the street to the house, as nearly all are up on a hillside. Garages are rare, and almost never attached, instead being next to the street. This makes for a very unique aesthetic that I really loved, so much so that when I found a house in town, with over 10 acres (impossible!), I convinced James we had to at least check it out, with the idea of possibly buying, renting out the house while we continue on our journey, then returning and building a new house on the other acreage, or selling the whole thing if we decided on a different area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_house.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_house&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We contacted a Realtor, and, perhaps luckily, found that the property has very little land that is close enough to flat to use, and the house needs more work than we&amp;rsquo;d be willing to do, especially remotely. I was a little bummed, but it&amp;rsquo;s ultimately for the best as we want to see more places before locking ourselves in somewhere. There&amp;rsquo;s also a challenge with older buildings in the area, as they are under special historic zoning and any changes have to go through a review board. Definitely not something we&amp;rsquo;d want to navigate from a remote position on top of the regular risks of hiring people to do work without being able to check it yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_ezri_park.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_ezri_park&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a nice playground in Deadwood too, a little over a mile from the RV park, so we ended a few runs there so she could get some play time in. Running in the area definitely gave me a challenge with elevation change, especially because the RV park is higher up so every run ended in a steep uphill. The RV Park also has it&amp;rsquo;s own history, with an abandoned mine on the property. We got to see some of the old machinery, and I found a rock with what I think is a little gold in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_ezri_mining.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_ezri_mining&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The temperature can change pretty rapidly there, we went from 80 degree days to 8ish inches of snow and back again over about a week&amp;rsquo;s span. Ezri of course loved the snow, but we quickly realized blue jeans aren&amp;rsquo;t sufficient snow gear, as they got soaked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the day after Labor Day:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_rv_park_snow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_rv_park_snow&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here&amp;rsquo;s three days later:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_rv_park_after.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_rv_park_after&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;lead&#34;&gt;Lead&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_homestake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_homestake&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead (pronounced &amp;ldquo;leed&amp;rdquo;, named after mining &amp;ldquo;leads&amp;rdquo;) is a small town of about 3,000 about 10 minutes from Deadwood, and has a lot of mining history. The Homestake Mine was started in 1876, and until it closed down in 2002, was the deepest mine in North America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_train.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_train&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_train_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_train_ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it was shut down, the town suffered and started to decline, but then in 2006, the Sanford Lab came to town and wanted to use the mine for neutrino research. Due to the depth of the mine, they are able to do research with far less white noise to have to account for. You can read more about it here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sanfordlab.org/&#34;&gt;https://www.sanfordlab.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_mine.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_mine&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of the deal, the Sanford lab put $20mil towards education reform in Lead/Deadwood (they share a single school district), which they plan to use to incorporate more STEM in the schools. There is also a newsletter that is sent to all Lead residents when the lab has updates on their projects, and they host monthly deep talks (until Covid-19, that is) with the community. The influx of STEM related education and people is something we find very appealing, and rare within such a small town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_train2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_train2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_mine_tank.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_mine_tank&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead&amp;rsquo;s downtown is walkable, though less tourist-focused than Deadwood. One thing we are finding with smaller towns, is the lack of regular open hours on businesses. There is one store in Lead that has ice cream and who knows what else that we wanted to see, but it was always closed anytime we had time (like the weekend), then we&amp;rsquo;d see it open on the way to dinner or some other off hour that we didn&amp;rsquo;t have the time to stop. Maybe we&amp;rsquo;ll make it back there to see it later on in our journey. There&amp;rsquo;s also a mine between Lead and Deadwood that you can tour underground and pan for gold that I wanted to see; we put it off one weekend, only to see &amp;lsquo;Closed for the season&amp;rsquo; posted afterwards, so that&amp;rsquo;s another one for if we make it back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_bank.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_bank&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead has a non-chain grocery store with a good selection, so we shopped there most of the time rather than making the drive to Spearfish. In the same building is a coffee shop that has become a bit of a community hangout spot; the owner lets people sign the entryway, and has tchotchkes and toys on display that have been brought in. We had a Las Vegas magnet that we added to the collection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_coffee.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_coffee&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead has a very vibrant Arts community, and there is even a Makerspace in the process of opening up! We&amp;rsquo;d love to be involved if we end up back in the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_makerspace.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_makerspace&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An antique piece of Artwork in a church that is now an Arts &amp;amp; Crafts shop:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_arts.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_arts&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead also has an opera house that normally has events at least every month. The list of events for the area has at least 4 things every month, from 5ks, snowshoe walks, and bicycle rides to parades and play performances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_opera.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_opera&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;rapid-city&#34;&gt;Rapid City&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_bront.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_bront&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nearest big-ish city for the area is Rapid City, with 75,000 people. It&amp;rsquo;s about 45 minutes drive from Deadwood. They have a dinosaur park that was built in the 30s, and from our observations, the artist must have been working from memory, as the inaccuracies were quite bad. Ezri loved it though, and since the dinosaurs are made of concrete, they allow the kids to play on them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_dino.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_dino&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_trex.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_trex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_triceratops.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_triceratops&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also went to a dinosaur museum that was more scientific, but Ezri got a bit scared as most of their exhibits were dinosaurs with the skin on, and she much prefers just the bones. Still, they had a digging area at the end with fake eggs and bones to uncover through the rubber &amp;lsquo;dirt&amp;rsquo;. She spent a long time there, and was upset when we finally left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_ezri_dig.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_ezri_dig&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_ezri_dig_home.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_ezri_dig_home&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing we found really odd is that the hotels in the area are apparently competing for who has the longest water-slide. Signs like &amp;lsquo;146 foot water-slide&amp;rsquo; were on each hotel we went past, with the water-slides jutting out from a corner of the hotel. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if this is a pretty normal thing, but it was a first for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rapid City has all your big city amenities, like Target and several sporting goods stores. There&amp;rsquo;s no Costco, but that&amp;rsquo;s not really something that&amp;rsquo;s very high up on our lists anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;next-stop&#34;&gt;Next Stop&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We pulled into our next stop, South Yankton Nebraska (Yankton South Dakota somewhat spans across the state lines) last week, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be staying 2 weeks here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;yankton.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;yankton&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
