<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cole Family</title>
    <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/</link>
    <description>  Cole Family</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.colefamily.page/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Black Hills of South Dakota (Lead / Deadwood / Rapid City)</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-09-28/black_hills.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-09-28/black_hills.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;blackhills_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;blackhills_ezri&#34; /&gt;While we stayed mostly in Deadwood, the whole area needs to be taken into account, so I&amp;rsquo;ve broken up some of this by city. This area has a lot of history so I&amp;rsquo;ll include some as it&amp;rsquo;s really necessary to see why we chose to visit and why it is now our top spot on our ranking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;spearfish&#34;&gt;Spearfish&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stayed a few days in Spearfish, due to the site in Deadwood not being available yet. We were able to find an RV park with a walking path that connected to a larger paved bike path. Ezri and I did a couple runs and walks through there and she found a love for trying to imitate the buzzing insects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;spearfish_trail.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;spearfish_trail&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This RV park also has daily ice cream socials, $3 a person for all you can eat, and we were thrilled to find it was outdoors and properly distanced. It was a really great way to meet and chat with our fellow RVers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;spearfish_koa.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;spearfish_koa&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spearfish is a medium small town, with about 10k people, and large enough to have a decent selection of restaurants, chain grocery stores, and a Wal-Mart. It&amp;rsquo;s only about a 25 minute drive from Deadwood, so our next hop was a short one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;spearfish_goodday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;spearfish_goodday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;spearfish_hatchery.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;spearfish_hatchery&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the cheap tires that came with the RV decided to develop bubbles already, so we also had to upgrade them while at our next stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;cheap_tires.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;cheap_tires&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;deadwood&#34;&gt;Deadwood&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_mansion.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_mansion&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stayed in an RV park nestled into a gulch for the rest of the 3 weeks we were in the area, and practically on the George S. Mickelson Trail, 108.8 miles of dirt trail that follows a former railroad. Perfect for running, walking, cycling, and open to snowmobiles in the winter, this is one of the reasons we wanted to check out the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_rv_park.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_rv_park&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwod_trail.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwod_trail&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deadwood is a small town of 1300, and has a famous history as an old west town, with a cemetery near the top of a mountain that has the graves of Wild Bill Hickok, Calamity Jane, and Seth Bullock. Around that area is also a hiking trail that Ezri and I took; though we accidentally went off trail and nearly doubled the distance, we had a lot of fun and there were some really great views.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_ezri_sitting.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_ezri_sitting&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the old West history, Deadwood&amp;rsquo;s main income source is tourism, and they have a great downtown with a lot of activities (though some are shut down due to covid). Every Thursday night is family night at the open air stage, and almost every day they have reenacted shootouts on main street every 2 hours for the tourists. There are also casinos with single deck blackjack, cheap prime rib buffets, and James says it really reminds him of old Vegas, back when he first got there. There&amp;rsquo;s also a coffee shop/glass blowing studio with some gorgeous pieces. They normally have glass blowing classes too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_glass_one.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_glass_one&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_glass_two.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_glass_two&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The area is very mountainous, so most of the houses are built multi-storied, with small footprints and tiny yards. They also frequently will have stairs leading from the street to the house, as nearly all are up on a hillside. Garages are rare, and almost never attached, instead being next to the street. This makes for a very unique aesthetic that I really loved, so much so that when I found a house in town, with over 10 acres (impossible!), I convinced James we had to at least check it out, with the idea of possibly buying, renting out the house while we continue on our journey, then returning and building a new house on the other acreage, or selling the whole thing if we decided on a different area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_house.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_house&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We contacted a Realtor, and, perhaps luckily, found that the property has very little land that is close enough to flat to use, and the house needs more work than we&amp;rsquo;d be willing to do, especially remotely. I was a little bummed, but it&amp;rsquo;s ultimately for the best as we want to see more places before locking ourselves in somewhere. There&amp;rsquo;s also a challenge with older buildings in the area, as they are under special historic zoning and any changes have to go through a review board. Definitely not something we&amp;rsquo;d want to navigate from a remote position on top of the regular risks of hiring people to do work without being able to check it yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_ezri_park.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_ezri_park&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a nice playground in Deadwood too, a little over a mile from the RV park, so we ended a few runs there so she could get some play time in. Running in the area definitely gave me a challenge with elevation change, especially because the RV park is higher up so every run ended in a steep uphill. The RV Park also has it&amp;rsquo;s own history, with an abandoned mine on the property. We got to see some of the old machinery, and I found a rock with what I think is a little gold in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_ezri_mining.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_ezri_mining&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The temperature can change pretty rapidly there, we went from 80 degree days to 8ish inches of snow and back again over about a week&amp;rsquo;s span. Ezri of course loved the snow, but we quickly realized blue jeans aren&amp;rsquo;t sufficient snow gear, as they got soaked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the day after Labor Day:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_rv_park_snow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_rv_park_snow&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here&amp;rsquo;s three days later:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;deadwood_rv_park_after.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;deadwood_rv_park_after&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;lead&#34;&gt;Lead&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_homestake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_homestake&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead (pronounced &amp;ldquo;leed&amp;rdquo;, named after mining &amp;ldquo;leads&amp;rdquo;) is a small town of about 3,000 about 10 minutes from Deadwood, and has a lot of mining history. The Homestake Mine was started in 1876, and until it closed down in 2002, was the deepest mine in North America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_train.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_train&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_train_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_train_ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it was shut down, the town suffered and started to decline, but then in 2006, the Sanford Lab came to town and wanted to use the mine for neutrino research. Due to the depth of the mine, they are able to do research with far less white noise to have to account for. You can read more about it here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sanfordlab.org/&#34;&gt;https://www.sanfordlab.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_mine.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_mine&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of the deal, the Sanford lab put $20mil towards education reform in Lead/Deadwood (they share a single school district), which they plan to use to incorporate more STEM in the schools. There is also a newsletter that is sent to all Lead residents when the lab has updates on their projects, and they host monthly deep talks (until Covid-19, that is) with the community. The influx of STEM related education and people is something we find very appealing, and rare within such a small town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_train2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_train2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_mine_tank.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_mine_tank&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead&amp;rsquo;s downtown is walkable, though less tourist-focused than Deadwood. One thing we are finding with smaller towns, is the lack of regular open hours on businesses. There is one store in Lead that has ice cream and who knows what else that we wanted to see, but it was always closed anytime we had time (like the weekend), then we&amp;rsquo;d see it open on the way to dinner or some other off hour that we didn&amp;rsquo;t have the time to stop. Maybe we&amp;rsquo;ll make it back there to see it later on in our journey. There&amp;rsquo;s also a mine between Lead and Deadwood that you can tour underground and pan for gold that I wanted to see; we put it off one weekend, only to see &amp;lsquo;Closed for the season&amp;rsquo; posted afterwards, so that&amp;rsquo;s another one for if we make it back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_bank.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_bank&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead has a non-chain grocery store with a good selection, so we shopped there most of the time rather than making the drive to Spearfish. In the same building is a coffee shop that has become a bit of a community hangout spot; the owner lets people sign the entryway, and has tchotchkes and toys on display that have been brought in. We had a Las Vegas magnet that we added to the collection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_coffee.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_coffee&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead has a very vibrant Arts community, and there is even a Makerspace in the process of opening up! We&amp;rsquo;d love to be involved if we end up back in the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_makerspace.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_makerspace&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An antique piece of Artwork in a church that is now an Crafts Shop:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_arts.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_arts&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead also has an opera house that normally has events at least every month. The list of events for the area has at least 4 things every month, from 5ks, snowshoe walks, and bicycle rides to parades and play performances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead_opera.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead_opera&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;rapid-city&#34;&gt;Rapid City&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_bront.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_bront&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nearest big-ish city for the area is Rapid City, with 75,000 people. It&amp;rsquo;s about 45 minutes drive from Deadwood. They have a dinosaur park that was built in the 30s, and from our observations, the artist must have been working from memory, as the inaccuracies were quite bad. Ezri loved it though, and since the dinosaurs are made of concrete, they allow the kids to play on them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_dino.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_dino&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_trex.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_trex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_triceratops.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_derpy_triceratops&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also went to a dinosaur museum that was more scientific, but Ezri got a bit scared as most of their exhibits were dinosaurs with the skin on, and she much prefers just the bones. Still, they had a digging area at the end with fake eggs and bones to uncover through the rubber &amp;lsquo;dirt&amp;rsquo;. She spent a long time there, and was upset when we finally left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_ezri_dig.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_ezri_dig&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rapidcity_ezri_dig_home.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rapidcity_ezri_dig_home&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing we found really odd is that the hotels in the area are apparently competing for who has the longest water-slide. Signs like &amp;lsquo;146 foot water-slide&amp;rsquo; were on each hotel we went past, with the water-slides jutting out from a corner of the hotel. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if this is a pretty normal thing, but it was a first for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rapid City has all your big city amenities, like target and several sporting goods stores. There&amp;rsquo;s no Costco, but that&amp;rsquo;s not really something that&amp;rsquo;s very high up on our lists anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;next-stop&#34;&gt;Next Stop&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We pulled into our next stop, South Yankton Nebraska (Yankton South Dakota somewhat spans across the state lines) last week, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be staying 2 weeks here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;yankton.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;yankton&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bozeman Montana and Sheridan Wyoming</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-09-08/bozeman_sheridan.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-09-08/bozeman_sheridan.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sunset.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunset&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;bozeman-montana&#34;&gt;Bozeman, Montana&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stayed in 2 separate RV parks in Bozeman, as we couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a continuous reservation available. Our first 2 days, we were at the Bozeman Hot Springs and Campground, but unfortunately we did not try the hot springs as they were busy with people not distancing or wearing masks. There was a playground right near our site though, so Ezri really enjoyed going there each day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_tube.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_tube&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that, we moved to Bear Canyon Campground for the rest of our stay, on the Southeast side of Bozeman. Being a little ways outside of town was less than ideal, as we found that most roads around Bozeman don&amp;rsquo;t have much, if any, shoulder. Right near us was a road that dead ended, but you could only get about 2 miles out before it ended. Overall, there were some good trails, but they were more mountain bike than manicured, and not well connected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sunset2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunset2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sunset_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunset_ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bozeman has a great walkable downtown with good restaurants, so that was a definite plus. Parking could be a little challenging, but that comes with a more populous area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bookstore.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bookstore&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went to the Museum of the Rockies twice while in Bozeman, Ezri has been really obsessed with bones lately (learning their names, asking if other people/animals have them, wanting me to take mine out so she can touch them, you know, normal stuff). Luckily they have a big collection of dinosaur bones, as well as reptile exhibits and an old homestead to tour. There&amp;rsquo;s also a planetarium star show, and with limited capacity due to distancing, we had to plan our second visit specifically to make the show. We got about 2 minutes in when the darkness and video of the inside of your head made Ezri too freaked out to continue. Maybe we&amp;rsquo;ll try a show like that again in a few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;trex_attack.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;trex_attack&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some great hiking trails in the surrounding area, so we picked a short, 1 mile out and back to see if Ezri will tolerate the hiking pack we have. Last time we used it, about a year and a half ago, she was too upset by being restricted and screamed until she fell asleep. This time, she fully understood the concept of being comfortably carried, loved the view from up high, and has been asking to hike again frequently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;james_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;james_ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;james_ezri2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;james_ezri2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_rebecca.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_rebecca&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bozeman tends to be a little drier than I want for plants and gardening, and the land prices are also a bit higher than we&amp;rsquo;d like. We&amp;rsquo;re pretty sure it&amp;rsquo;s off the list for future places to live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;sheridan-wyoming&#34;&gt;Sheridan, Wyoming&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rv_setup.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rv_setup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The drive from Bozeman to Sheridan was supposed to be right within our regular pull, just shy of 4 hours drive time with a stop at the halfway point taking it to 4.5ish. This was not in the cards for us, unfortunately, and we ended up having to stop an additional 3 times for potty breaks (2 of them false alarms). Our total time ended up being a little over 6 hours, so we all arrived a teensy bit grumpy. Luckily, our reserved site was a pull-through, which is super easy to get the RV into. We lucked out too, that we were right next to the playground in the park, so Ezri had a lot of fun during our stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tricycle2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tricycle2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tricycle.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tricycle&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are paved paths that cover a good amount of the city, but with highs in the upper 90s to over 100, we didn&amp;rsquo;t get out on them many times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;dad_park.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dad_park&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The downtown is walkable and has some nice restaurants, one of which has a aquaponics installation we really liked. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time we&amp;rsquo;ve seen a setup that had taken looks into account, and Ezri loved watching the fish in the bottom of it. Definitely going to be filing that away for future consideration once we have a house, as I think something like that could go well on our back porch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;aquaponics.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;aquaponics&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;aquaponics2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;aquaponics2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the high heat and dry climate, Sheridan is also going to be out of the running for our final home, but we enjoyed our time there for sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;horns.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;horns&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;horn_money.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;horn_money&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Sheridan, we drove 3 hours to Spearfish, South Dakota (for a two-day stay before Deadwood / Lead), with, thankfully, only 1 potty break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sunset_sheridan.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunset_sheridan&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalispell and Helena Montana</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-08-02/kalispell_helena.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-08-02/kalispell_helena.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;kalispell-montana&#34;&gt;Kalispell, Montana&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;somers.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;somers&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lake_dad_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lake_dad_ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kalispell is definitely a contender for us, it has friendly people and beautiful landscapes. The weather proves to a be a little unpredictable: due to the mountains in the area, high winds whip through periodically and the weather can change rapidly. One day we went from blue sunny skies to high winds, rain, and hail within about 3 hours. Definitely makes for some excitement, but also some frustration; we got all dressed for a bike ride one morning only to have it start raining the second we got in the saddle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lead.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lead&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;whitehead.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;whitehead&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of bike riding, we finally got everything in place to go on a family ride. Due to the spike in demand for bicycles, we had a heck of a time finding the bike trailer we wanted for Ezri. It allows her to pedal while also being more of a chair with safety straps so we can be sure she won&amp;rsquo;t fall off. We only went for 10 miles as we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to push either Ezri or myself too hard, but it was very enjoyable, and she definitely wants to go more often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bike.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rbike.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rbike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bike trails made for excellent runs, walks, and rides. We&amp;rsquo;re going to miss them now that we&amp;rsquo;ve left the area. Unlike in some places we&amp;rsquo;ve been, the trails are quite long and decently interconnected. Kila, which is about 15 miles outside of Kalispell, could be reached by cycling trails from where we stayed. If we decide to move to the area, Kila is probably where we&amp;rsquo;d end up settling. It&amp;rsquo;s a very small town, with 20+ acre parcels available for good prices, and still easy to access the amenities of Kalispell nearby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;railstotrails.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;railstotrails&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;biketrail.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;biketrail&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While checking out the area, we came across a Fire Station fund-raiser, and were able to climb inside some of the fire trucks. Ezri had a blast pretending to drive, but was disappointed they weren&amp;rsquo;t going to let us take them for an actual spin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;firetruck.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;firetruck&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_drive.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_drive&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lake_rebecca_ezri.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lake_rebecca_ezri&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We visited the &amp;lsquo;Miracle of America&amp;rsquo; museum, which had a little of everything to look at. We felt like we could have come back and spent another 10 hours and still likely not seen everything. One of our favorite things was some working Nickelodeon pianos they had that still accepted quarters, and a boat ride that worked on dimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_tractor.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_tractor&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_boat.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_boat&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_desk.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_desk&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Glacier National Park is one of the reasons a lot of people would see Kalispell, we drove up one day, but unfortunately the best part of the park, &amp;lsquo;Going to the Sun Road&amp;rsquo; was closed. We still visited the beach of the river for a while, and Ezri had a lot of fun playing in the sand and water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;river.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;river&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;river_bucket.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;river_bucket&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The day before we had to leave town, James got up super early and rode his bike up the &amp;lsquo;Going to the Sun Road&amp;rsquo;, as they allow bicycles while it is still closed to cars. It was about 42 miles round trip, but the steep part was 3000 feet of climbing in 10 miles. You can see his &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.strava.com/activities/3747732304&#34;&gt;Strava ride here with a lot more pictures&lt;/a&gt; than just those below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;glacier2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;glacier2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;glacier_tunnel.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;glacier_tunnel&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;glacier3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;glacier3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;glacier.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;glacier&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The day after we left Kalispell, they opened the rest of Glacier to cars. I&amp;rsquo;m bummed I missed seeing the best parts, but glad James was able to do his epic bike ride before we left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;helena-montana&#34;&gt;Helena, Montana&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;helena_a.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;helena_a&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next stop was Helena, Montana, for 2 weeks. This one was added by me, as looking online, I thought this was a real potential candidate. Helena is the capitol of Montana, and was at one point the richest city in the state due to successful mining operations. There are some beautiful old houses and buildings in their downtown area, and they have a walkable section that is closed off to cars and lined with cute shops and restaurants. We bought a few more games for Ezri than we probably should have at a toy store there, and I bought a half pound of chocolates at a chocolate shop that I&amp;rsquo;m now trying to not to eat all at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Helena has an average of 300 sunny days a year, so it&amp;rsquo;s dry and the natural vegetation tends more towards sagebrush than trees or grasses. Some of the lots we looked at were up at the edge of the mountains and reminded me a lot of Mt. Charleston outside of Las Vegas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;helena_ride.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;helena_ride&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;helena_ride2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;helena_ride2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took Ezri to the Black Sandy State Park on the edge of Lake Helena and spent a few hours in the water. She was having a great time until she went a little too far out, slipped, and dunked herself. Even so, anytime we go near or mention any kind of water, she wants to go dip her toes in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;helena_lake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;helena_lake&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_helena_pbj.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_helena_pbj&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, while Helena was nice and the people were friendly, it was just too deserty. While there, though, we heard from multiple people that we HAD to check out Bozeman, Montana. We were able to finagle the schedule, and that is our next stop.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Distancing in Joseph Oregon</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-06-20/joseph.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-06-20/joseph.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;joseph1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;joseph1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whew! Time really flies, been meaning to write another post for a while. We just left Joseph, Oregon after staying there about 3 months. With things mostly shut down, we decided it was best to hunker down in one place until things started opening back up again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joseph is just north of Wallowa Lake, and we made it to the north end of the lake a few times for Ezri to play in the water. If she had her way, we&amp;rsquo;d never leave. We spent an hour on a rented paddle boat out on the South end of the lake, Ezri alternated between helping pedal and leaning over the edge to pick up sticks or splash in the water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_lake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_lake&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joseph has a very walkable, picturesque Main Street we both ran and walked up and down many times. Our RV Park was just off of Main Street, so having direct access was really nice. There are bronze sculptures all around the town, and Ezri&amp;rsquo;s favorite by far is a mom and baby horse &amp;lsquo;hugging&amp;rsquo;. She insisted we get a picture in front of them. There are a few different restaurants we enjoyed, an old style soda fountain and ice cream shop, and a chocolate shop I got a few too many chocolate truffles from. The mix of small town and tourist attraction made for a really nice culture, and I think we&amp;rsquo;ll have a hard time topping the welcoming, well maintained main street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_horses.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_horses&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first month, we were almost the only ones in the RV park, but after that we got some lovely neighbors who we had a lot of fun talking with, Anna and Jeanne (from 6 feet of course!). We have missed having close connections while on the road, and it was so nice to make some friends. They also gave me an awesome haircut as a parting gift, which I&amp;rsquo;m really enjoying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;anna_joanne.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;anna_joanne&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;family_table.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;family_table&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had Easter in Joseph, and were worried Ezri would miss having other kids around for egg hunting. We should have known she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind at all; she was too focused on finding all the eggs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;easter.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;easter&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Ezri getting a little older, I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to start doing more projects, so I&amp;rsquo;ve made a few masks for us, as well as 2 dresses for Ezri. I&amp;rsquo;ve restarted a half-done knitting project too, and am looking forward to wrapping it up and starting on another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mask.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mask&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;dress.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dress&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James has gotten back on his bike, to discover that a road bike and dirt roads don&amp;rsquo;t go together very well. He upgraded to a gravel bike (James says: &lt;a href=&#34;https://salsacycles.com/bikes/warroad/2019_warroad_carbon_force_1_650&#34;&gt;2019 Salsa Warroad Force 1 650b&lt;/a&gt; with a 48T chainring upgrade + Power2Max NGEco power meter), and convinced me to get a new gravel bike too. We also got Ezri a trailer that lets her help pedal. She has been practicing on it, but the weather turned cold and windy right as we got it, so we haven&amp;rsquo;t gone out as a family yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;james.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;james&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bike.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s an old railroad that cuts through the edge of Joseph but no longer has trains on it. It&amp;rsquo;s great for walking on, and there&amp;rsquo;s a company that has pedal cars you can rent to take on it too. By the time they were allowed to reopen, we only had 1 weekend to try them, and it got too windy and cold, so we&amp;rsquo;ve got something on the list to do next time we&amp;rsquo;re in the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;railroad.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;railroad&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, Joseph has friendly people and beautiful views, though it lacks diversity and access to stores (the nearest big box is WalMart in La Grande, over 1.5 hours away). We also would have about a 2 hour drive to the nearest airport, and while James isn&amp;rsquo;t traveling weekly anymore, he&amp;rsquo;ll still be visiting clients about once a quarter post-covid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-states-in-under-48-hours&#34;&gt;4 states in under 48 hours&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;family.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;family&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;rv.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rv&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leaving Joseph, we decided to break our trip into 2 days rather than make the nearly 8 hour drive in one. We drove from Oregon, through Washington, then stopped overnight in Coeur D&amp;rsquo;Alene, Idaho in an RV park with lake access. Ezri played in the water even though it was a little chilly. The RV park was nice, but huge compared to the tiny one we came from. It felt strange to see so many RVs and people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri_cda.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri_cda&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day, we grabbed breakfast and headed out to our current location: Kalispell, Montana. Kalispell is a smallish town of about 30,000 people, with amenities like Target, Costco, and JoAnn&amp;rsquo;s. The RV park we chose &lt;a href=&#34;https://montanabasecamp.com/&#34;&gt;Montana Basecamp&lt;/a&gt; is on a well maintained bike/jogging path; we don&amp;rsquo;t even need to get on a road to access it from the RV park. We plan to stay here for a month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;basecamp.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;basecamp&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proving that the world is much smaller than we think, James saw a familiar Wi-Fi access point while setting up, to discover his coworker and fellow RVer Michael Kidd and his wife Lehnanne is staying a few sites down from us&amp;hellip; We actually first met them in person about a year ago in Las Vegas just before buying our fifth wheel! It was great back then talking about what living on the road would be like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can check out their travel blog at &lt;a href=&#34;https://turtleherding.com/&#34;&gt;https://turtleherding.com/&lt;/a&gt;. We look forward to catching up with them while we&amp;rsquo;re here!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bumpy Road to Pacific City and Cascade Locks</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-04-11/bumpy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-04-11/bumpy.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Apologies, this is a little late, it was written on April 3rd; the next post about Joseph, OR will be forthcoming.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our last few weeks in Fall City didn&amp;rsquo;t go as we had planned, as we got a call in the middle of the night that James&amp;rsquo;s step-mom, Kim, had passed away. Luckily James&amp;rsquo;s work has paid bereavement leave and my work can be flexible, allowing us to fly out to Tennessee to support his dad. The funeral was beautiful, and we were able to catch up with friends and family we didn&amp;rsquo;t see during our Christmas trip out there. We were all shocked by her passing, and will miss her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tn_bug.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tn_bug&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James has transitioned within Red Hat to a new role of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redhat.com/en/blog/being-technical-account-manager-tam-day-life&#34;&gt;Technical Account Manager&lt;/a&gt; which is mostly remote and will only require travel a few times a quarter. We are very excited for the increased time we&amp;rsquo;ll spend together, and it&amp;rsquo;s nice to not have to worry about proximity to an airport when planning our stops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The drive from Fall City to Pacific City Oregon was relatively uneventful. Some of the mountain roads had sunken grade and other damage that made for a bumpy ride. The RV Park we stayed in was really nice, and the stay was free for us since we have a membership to Thousand Trails. The membership cost just a little more than a 2 week stay, and gives us free stays in member RV parks as long as it&amp;rsquo;s been at least a week since we last were in one and we don&amp;rsquo;t stay longer than 14 days. It&amp;rsquo;ll be a while until we&amp;rsquo;re at a location with another Thousand Trails park, but we&amp;rsquo;ve already more than made up for the price of membership by staying 2 weeks free in Fall City, then 2 weeks free in Pacific City.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;family_pacificcity.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;family_pacificcity&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pacific City is directly on the coast, and has some great local restaurants. We were able to walk directly from the RV Park to the beach. Ezri loved playing in the sand, even though it was a bit chilly and windy each time we went. When we first arrived, we opted to eat out more than normal, and I am so glad we did, since we barely beat the spread of COVID-19 and subsequent closing of dine-in areas. The people we talked to were friendly, and we discovered most of the houses in Pacific City are vacation rentals. Not sure how that would impact the overall culture, but it seemed a little too tourist heavy to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pacificcity_rock.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pacificcity_rock&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The RV Park we stayed at is unfortunately in an area with minimal cell signal. We were unable to make/receive phone calls from our site; text messages were hit and miss. Luckily our AT&amp;amp;T connection we use for wifi was slightly stronger, and we had enough Internet to stay connected via hangouts and other tools, but to get any work done we had to either go to the Family Center or a nearby coffee shop. The Family Center has a pool table, ping pong, a few arcade games, and a room of toys for younger kids, as well as several tables and chairs, so I took Ezri there almost every day so she could play while I worked for an hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;bunnies.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bunnies&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;mommy_baby.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mommy_baby&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few miles south of Pacific City is Lincoln City, we spent the day out there shopping in their outlet mall for new clothes for Ezri, since she&amp;rsquo;d pretty much outgrown all of her 2T stuff. The town seems more kid-friendly, one store had a table covered in sand and toys with a sign encouraging kids to play, and a coffee shop there had games out on every table. It was hard to get her to go with us into the clothing stores since all she wanted to do was play marbles again! Overall, I really enjoyed the vibe and availability of stores in Lincoln City.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;North of Pacific City, we went up to Netarts and Oceanside. Both had some lovely restaurants with fresh seafood. Oceanside&amp;rsquo;s beach sometimes has geodes, so we walked along it looking for them. We found a few tiny ones, along with shells, and Ezri had fun digging in all of the rocks and sand. We also drove up a bit further to Cape Mears to the shortest, stubbiest lighthouse we&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;lighthouse.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lighthouse&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With stricter directives that are practically a shelter in place order coming to Oregon, we spent the latter half of our stay mostly within the RV Park. They locked all of the buildings, so no more Family Center, but I got furloughed right around the same time and no longer had the need to work. James still needed to get work done, so he would drive the truck to the Family Center or the coffee shop, connect to their Wi-Fi, and work from within the truck. Not the most ideal situation, but it worked. Since we were inside so much, we decided it was the perfect time to potty train. Using the 3 day method right before a car trip wasn&amp;rsquo;t ideal, but we went for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;coffee_shop.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;coffee_shop&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, James&amp;rsquo;s brother, Joseph, ended up in the hospital while we were in Pacific City; hours from the nearest airport. We discussed having James fly out to see him, but were worried about potentially spreading COVID-19, as well as taking time off from a new job right after taking bereavement leave. James was at least able to use up his Southwest miles to fly out his mom and dad, but they were unable to get into the hospital when they arrived. Due to virus concerns, they shut it down to visitors. After a few days, Joseph was discharged and seems to be pretty much back to normal, which was a big relief.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our drive to the next stop, Cascade Locks, Oregon, was only about 3 hours. Since Ezri was so new to potty training, we planned a few stops. The first one was harder to get to than we&amp;rsquo;d thought, so we took a chance and skipped it. At the 2 hour mark we stopped at a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s for lunch and tried to have a potty break, to find that she is not OK using restaurant bathrooms. Afterwards, we drove the rest of the way to the RV Park, and then she used her little potty in the back of my car. I was shocked she made it about 3.5 hours without any accidents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;cascadelocks.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;cascadelocks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve been in Cascade Locks for about a week and a half, and will be leaving on Saturday. Technically the RV park we are in is closed, but the owners aren&amp;rsquo;t kicking out people like us who aren&amp;rsquo;t vacationers. The RV Park is right next to the railroad tracks, and while the trains were exciting initially, they run most often during the night and have woken us all up several times. We&amp;rsquo;re looking forward to getting a quiet night&amp;rsquo;s sleep at the next place. We are disappointed we haven&amp;rsquo;t really had an opportunity to check out the area or culture much, we can see some amazing cycling/walking/jogging trails by the highway and the maps show many trail-heads, but the weather has been a bit rainy and cold whenever we have the time to go, and the trail-heads look like they are closed anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;cascadelocks2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;cascadelocks2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next stop is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nytimes.com/2017/07/20/travel/wallowa-valley-mountains-joseph-oregon-culture.html&#34;&gt;Joseph, Oregon&lt;/a&gt;. We originally planned to stay 2 weeks there, but are discussing whether we should stay until the socialization limitations are lifted, as the whole point of this journey is to get a feel for different places, and we aren&amp;rsquo;t able to do that without interacting with people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Since we updated this post late, here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of part of the drive to Joseph, Oregon:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;joseph_drive.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;joseph_drive&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall City Washington and Busy Busy Holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-02-16/holidays.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2020-02-16/holidays.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey friends, been meaning to write an update for a while, so many things have built up to update you on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re staying in an RV Resort near Fall City, a town of about 2,000 people. We are about 30 minutes from Issaquah, and 20 minutes from Andrew, Jason, and Ben (my brothers). This spot is more private than some of the others we&amp;rsquo;ve stayed at, and we accidentally got a site that is right in the middle of where a lot of the employees are staying. That has been a benefit as we have gotten to know them well over this time, we have consistent neighbors, and one of our neighbors even volunteered to watch Daisy for us when we were out of town for Christmas. The weather here has been very wet, this is one of the most rainy Januarys they&amp;rsquo;ve had in several years. Such a huge difference from Las Vegas weather, and it&amp;rsquo;s nice to see green things, but I&amp;rsquo;m a bit sick of the mud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;snow-rv.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Snowy RV&#34; /&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;flood.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Flooded Road&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We settled in just in time for Thanksgiving. It was wonderful to be able to spend it with family and friends after being on the road for a few months. The lack of friends and family nearby has been the hardest part of RV living.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ezri turned 2 on December 13th, we had a little party in the rec center at the RV Park, and Andrew, Jason, Ben, and their families were able to join us. Ezri loves playing with her cousins, and though she didn&amp;rsquo;t really care for the cake, she did enjoy the pizza and presents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-bday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ezri&#39;s Birthday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Debbie, Steve, and Todd were able to come out for an early Christmas, and Ben hosted all of us at his roommate&amp;rsquo;s house. It was wonderful seeing everyone. Emily and her family weren&amp;rsquo;t able to come out, but she sent a giant order of fancy breads and pastries that were delicious. Ezri and Nathan loved playing in the shredded paper they came packed in, and loved being &amp;lsquo;monsters&amp;rsquo; by covering themselves head to toe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-cousins.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ezri and Cousins&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next week, we flew out to Tennessee to see James&amp;rsquo;s family. It had been about 8 years since we last went out there, so the trip was long overdue. When so much time has passed, it&amp;rsquo;s always hard to reconcile just how much people have changed with what we have in our heads. James&amp;rsquo;s dad and stepmom are helping out a relative with a daughter that is one, so Ezri got to play with lots of toys while we were there, and she enjoyed having baby playtime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-tn.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ezri in Tennessee&#34; /&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;ezri-fish.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ezri at Aquarium&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In mid-January, Ezri and I made a 7 hour (each way) drive to Grants Pass, Oregon to see my Grandma and Grandpa, and were joined by Emily (my sister) and her 2 youngest. We also got to visit with my cousin who lives in the area and has 2 daughters near Ezri&amp;rsquo;s age. It was a great visit, Ezri had so much fun with her cousins (and second cousins), and I loved the chance to catch up with Emily in person. It was also nice to find out that we can drive for so long without any major meltdowns. On both drives Ezri dumped her bag of snacks all over herself and the car, but Cheeto stains and having to vacuum were definitely not the worst that could have happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-gran.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ness Family&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My license and car registration were up for renewal around my birthday, and the DMV wouldn&amp;rsquo;t let me renew online, so after much discussion, we decided I&amp;rsquo;d fly out for a quick 24 hour trip to Las Vegas to get it taken care of. After 2.5 hours sitting at the DMV, my license is good for another 8 years, and my car registration is good until March 2021. I was a little worried that Ezri would give James a hard time in my absence, since she and I rarely spend any time apart. They had a grand time, and I think she hardly noticed I was gone. James took her to an event at Home Depot where they introduce kids to tools, and she made a cute heart decoration. We&amp;rsquo;ll be seeking out these events in the future for sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-heart.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ezri Heart&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Issaquah has a gym here with a daycare, but unique to them is that next door is a sports center with bounce houses and inflatable slides. They have an agreement that the gym daycare kids can come over and bounce, so Ezri loves going to the gym. We have been making it about 3 days a week on average, and I&amp;rsquo;m feeling like I&amp;rsquo;m making decent progress in getting back in shape. I will be sad to leave the gym behind when we move on to the next place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of moving on, we have &lt;a href=&#34;../map&#34;&gt;updated the map with the tentative route for 2020&lt;/a&gt;! Our goal is to reach Ann Arbor, Michigan just after Halloween, and spend the winter there with Emily. Our reservation here is up on March 7th, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be heading South to Pacific City, Oregon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../map&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;route.png&#34; alt=&#34;route&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walla Walla Washington</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-12-10/wallawalla.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-12-10/wallawalla.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bluevalleyrv.com/&#34;&gt;Blue Valley RV Park&lt;/a&gt; we stayed at in Walla Walla had a great paved path that connected to the park, then went alongside a golf-course, some fields, and a few neighborhoods. With adding a few loops around a track that wasn&amp;rsquo;t far off the path, I was able to run a full 10k. Unfortunately, I also discovered a recurring leg pain I thought I had rested away was not actually gone yet. Doing some research into proper gait and posture when running with a stroller, and hopefully I can get that one solved soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The town itself was really great; The downtown area was very walkable, and there were vineyards and wine tasting rooms everywhere. We found a wonderful restaraunt called &lt;a href=&#34;https://maplecountercafe.com/&#34;&gt;Maple Counter Cafe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;breakfast1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;breakfast1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;breakfast2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;breakfast2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Walla Walla didn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of indoor kids activities due to its size, but they did have a Children&amp;rsquo;s Museum. Ezri had a blast there; they had a water table with sand and toys so you could make dams, redirect the water, and generally just make a mess. They also had a climbing wall with a slide at the top that she had a lot of fun on, and a giant tube with a fan underneath it that you could put scarves and ribbons under: the air would catch them, spin them up, and out the top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sandbox2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sandbox2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sandbox1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sandbox1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were very lucky that we were in town when a local business was celebrating a big anniversary. They threw a party at the local fairgrounds, and Ezri and I got to go. (James was in Las Vegas, more about that next.) At first, the sheer number of people and noise level was a lot for her to handle, and she needed to be held while covering her ears. After about 20 minutes though, she relaxed a little. I was surprised when Ezri wanted to go into a bounce house with the bigger kids, but figured worst case I&amp;rsquo;d go in there and get her if it was too much. She LOVED it. Once I even had to tell some older girls who thought she was too young to stop holding her hands and let her jump. They also had a huge inflatable slide that Ezri wanted to try. I thought the climb up might be too much, but sure enough, she went for it and had a ball. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to catch a picture of her at the top, but you can see her right after she got to the bottom of the slide. She was the last one out of the bounce house. She didn&amp;rsquo;t want to leave and I had to go in and get her so they could shut it down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;slide.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;slide&#34; /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our house is finally, completely, sold!&lt;/strong&gt; James had to spend a weekend in Las Vegas packing up all of the furniture we had left for staging and moving it into storage. We loved that house, but it&amp;rsquo;s great to no longer be paying for the mortgage and utilities on top of our expenses on the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;storage.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;storage&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Walla Walla was very foggy, at least half of the days we were there had fog, with most of those being bad enough for there to be weather advisories. I can confidently say I do not enjoy being in fog for more than a day at a time, it starts to feel a little claustrophobic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;park3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;park3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;parknight2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;parknight2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, my car started acting up about halfway through our stay. When it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t turn over one morning, I assumed a dead battery, but testing at the AutoZone didn&amp;rsquo;t uncover any obvious issue other than the battery being low. Testing the alternator revealed a too high ripple so we thought just replacing the battery wouldn&amp;rsquo;t solve our problem. I bought a battery jump starter, and used that for most of the time we were there, but the last few days the battery was so bad that the electronics weren&amp;rsquo;t acting right, headlights would turn off randomly, so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t safe to drive anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My car is still covered under warranty, but the nearest dealership was over 200 miles away in Tacoma, Washington. Luckily Mini roadside assistance policy is a free tow to the nearest dealership. I had to remind the worker I talked to of that before they agreed to cover it, but ultimately won out and got them to pay for the tow. Ezri and I rode in the truck to Issaquah with James, which was both good and bad. It was nice being all together, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize just how much comfort I get from following behind the RV and being able to see there are no issues with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once we got the car to the dealership, they declared all that was wrong was a bad battery, and covered that under the warranty. I&amp;rsquo;m still sceptical, but luckily we are close by so if this battery dies too, at least it won&amp;rsquo;t be as big of an ordeal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mini.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mini&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate that we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to spend a little more time together as a family in Walla Walla because of the Las Vegas trip, but we wanted to get over the mountains before the ice and snow hit &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wsdot.com/traffic/passes/snoqualmie/&#34;&gt;Snoqualmie Pass&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;drive1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;drive1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;drive2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;drive2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We arrived in Fall City, Washington near Issaquah on November 23rd. We just paid for a long-term stay until March 7th since James will be working in the area for the next couple of months at least, and it should be a nice place to wait out Winter. We&amp;rsquo;ll have another post about our last few weeks here at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rvonthego.com/washington/tall-chief-rv-camping-resort/&#34;&gt;Tall Chief RV Resort&lt;/a&gt; in the next few days, stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;tallchief1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tallchief1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;James Note: Sorry for so few pictures of Walla Walla without fog, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t always dreary looking, we were just busy!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Idaho Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-11-07/homedale.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-11-07/homedale.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Boise Idaho area was beautiful, we visited at the perfect time to see the leaves changing color. On our drive we saw several fields of various crops, including hops, corn, alfalfa, apples, and pomegranates. While it got a little chilly at night, most days it was warm enough that we could bundle up and spend time outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;snakeriver.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;snakeriver&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We decided to stay at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://snakeriverrv.com/&#34;&gt;Snake River Resort RV&lt;/a&gt; park outside of Boise in Homedale Idaho. It is on the river, with our morning view consisting of ducks and fog rolling on the river each morning. They have a little walking trail that takes you around the neighboring alfalfa field. Ezri&amp;rsquo;s favorite part of the walk on it was finding a grocery bag that had gotten stuck on the fence, freeing it, and filling it with rocks she found along the trail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Boise, we visited a Children&amp;rsquo;s Museum, which was much more of a toy collection than a museum, so right up Ezri&amp;rsquo;s alley. She loved playing on a horse that you press down on the &amp;lsquo;stirrups&amp;rsquo; to move forward, and had to spend time hugging all of the stuffed animals in their play vet&amp;rsquo;s office. She also enjoyed the Magna Tiles, especially destroying any creation I put together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;horse.gif&#34; alt=&#34;horse&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also went to &lt;a href=&#34;https://warhawkairmuseum.org/&#34;&gt;The Warhawk Air Museum&lt;/a&gt; in Nampa, which turned out to be a little too hands-off for Ezri (note from James: &lt;em&gt;definitely check it out if you like restored warbirds, especially the P40, my favorite. They had an incredible amount of historical information.&lt;/em&gt;). They did have 2 sealed domes with gloves attached that are like the ones sometimes used in space to perform experiments when the chemicals involved can be dangerous to the people or equipment. They had a Duplo set inside one, and a Lego set inside the other. Ezri enjoyed trying to grab the pieces with the giant gloves, but also kept trying to get the pieces out by pulling them through the glove holes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James and Ezri created a Jack-O-Lantern together on the Saturday before Halloween, and we did a trunk or treat on the Sunday.
&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin-collage.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin-collage&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pumpkin.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pumpkin&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Halloween, they have a trick or treat event where businesses throughout their downtown area opt in to handing out candy. It worked out great for us because we didn&amp;rsquo;t have to intrude on a neighborhood we weren&amp;rsquo;t really a part of. She was pretty shy for most of it, and only spoke to one adult who was dressed up as a butterfly. She definitely was understanding the concept though, and would hold out her bucket for each place we stopped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mirror.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mirror&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;costume.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;costume&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ezri is almost through eating all of her candy, her favorites have been lollipops by far, but she also liked gummy bears and skittles a lot. I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to when she finishes her candy; I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to keep up with all the sticky hand prints she&amp;rsquo;s been putting on the furniture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;sucker.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sucker&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We moved onward to Walla Walla Washington on November 2nd, and so far it&amp;rsquo;s been great as well, we&amp;rsquo;ll have more updates soon! (Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to checkout the &lt;a href=&#34;../map/&#34;&gt;Route Map&lt;/a&gt; link for current location and planned stops)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;route.png&#34; alt=&#34;route&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada Wrap-Up - Great Basin and Elko NV</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-10-26/great-basin-elko.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-10-26/great-basin-elko.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, James here!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our final week in Ely, we drove out to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nps.gov/grba/&#34;&gt;Great Basin National Park&lt;/a&gt; where we got to see Wheeler Peak, the second highest mountain in Nevada.  This is a wonderful, out of the way park that we really should&amp;rsquo;ve spent a few more days exploring. Wheeler Peak is 13,065 ft high, and you can drive to over 10,000 ft in your car - It really hits home just how high you are when you realize that if you were in an airliner, you could go to the bathroom at this height on a normal flight :-)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;wheeler-peak.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;wheeler-peak&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After visiting the park, including the Peak and doing the Lehman Cave tour, we stopped by an amazing little gourmet restaurant called &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.stargazernevada.com/&#34;&gt;Kerouac&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt; started by a couple from New York who started it in 2017. There&amp;rsquo;s not much else on Highway 50, that&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s known as &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;The Loneliest Road in America&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;. You might go for dozens of miles without seeing anyone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also stopped by the &lt;a href=&#34;http://parks.nv.gov/parks/ward-charcoal-ovens&#34;&gt;Ward Charcoal Ovens&lt;/a&gt; only used for three years during the 1870s silver boom. Ezri loved playing with the echoes in the ovens, and the surrounding country-side was beautiful and made for a great little day hike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-oven.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-oven&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;echo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;echo&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We wrapped up Ely by Rebecca and Ezri learning to bake together - She loves to be involved in any activity we&amp;rsquo;re doing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-stirring.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-stirring&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ezri-rebecca-stirring.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ezri-rebecca-stirring&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;short-stay-in-elko-nv&#34;&gt;Short stay in Elko, NV&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now, from Rebecca (since James had to travel to Orlando for work):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ely was a great transition for Elko, since Ezri got used to the sound of trains and was no longer scared of them. All of the RV parks are close to the train tracks, and trains were a normal occurrence for us. Elko was a short stay, only a week. Unfortunately, since we drove on Saturday, and were setting up the RV Sunday, James didn&amp;rsquo;t get much of a chance to see the town before we headed out again the following Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ezri and I went to the Chamber of Commerce, which is run from an old fort and has historic wagons and buildings on the lot. The only thing Ezri was really into there was the rocking chairs on their front porch. Next door to that is the Northeastern Nevada Museum, which has some examples of local rocks and gems, and historic clothing and daily living items. They also have a wing with over 200 taxidermy animals from all over the world, many of which I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen before. &lt;img src=&#34;rocking-chair.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rocking-chair&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got our first glimpse of real fall, and a neighbor loaned us their rake so we could make a pile to play in. Ezri loved playing in the leaves, and helping remake the pile each time it spread out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;leaves-play.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;leaves-play&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;leaves.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;leaves&#34; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;grass.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;grass&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The drive to Boise was rather eventful for us. Due to 2 RV parks near Boise having the same name, and a bit of assumption on our part that we were navigating to the same place, a quick stop for gas caused me to take an entirely different route than James, that was an hour longer. By the time we realized the issue, doubling back would cause the same amount of time difference, so I corrected the destination and continued on. We both experienced snow, hail, rain, and extremely high winds on our drive. At one point, my heart rate was high for long enough that FitBit automatically logged an aerobic activity for me, lasting 23 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;onward-to-boise-id&#34;&gt;Onward to Boise, ID&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like Rebecca said, our drive to Boise was pretty interesting, so here is a photo of my snowy drive, at least from before it really started sleeting and before the wind blew so hard and I was too white-knuckled holding the RV on the road to take many pictures!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;snowy.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;snowy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Aboard to Ely Nevada!</title>
      <link>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-10-08/ely.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.colefamily.page/posts/2019-10-08/ely.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ely_train.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re getting close to the end of our stay in Ely, and it&amp;rsquo;s been a really great time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a train museum here, with a steam train and a diesel train you can buy tickets for. We rode the steam train, and Ezri had so much fun talking about the train and imitating the choo choo. The ride itself takes 90 minutes, with historical information peppered throughout. We were surprised to learn that in the early 1900s, Ely was the biggest town in Nevada, and had the tallest building (the Nevada Hotel, a whopping 6 stories high). The amount of ore that the trains have hauled during the 1900s was staggering as well, how much was needed for a small amount of copper was very surprising. Ezri has been getting better and better about conquering her fears; it was awesome seeing Ezri go from mildly terrified when we first arrived to absolutely excited and wanting to get closer to the train.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also went up to Garnet Hill, and found a few super tiny garnets. We&amp;rsquo;re planning on going up to Great Basin National Park this week, and James is trying to convince me we can find space to store a few fishing poles in the RV so we can go fishing at Cave Lake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a bit colder than we anticipated, but true to high desert, the temperature varies greatly from the night to day. We have gotten a good system of using the propane heater at night while it&amp;rsquo;s below 30, and opening the windows during the day to keep from going above 80 inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wifi has been slow at best, which I suppose we should have expected (James said he totally saw this one coming). It&amp;rsquo;s done wonders for our streaming habits, and I felt nostalgic today trying to download a file, and watching the estimated time go from 2 days to 3 days, to 5 days, to a download failure. We ordered a Netgear Nighthawk N1 LTE Modem with external antennas, and a few sim cards from Google Fi to get our own network going, a cost we had hoped to hold off until after the house sells, but a necessity for staying sane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We knew we were going to a remote area, with much fewer amenities, but it really didn&amp;rsquo;t sink in until we saw this shirt in the gift shop. The nearest Walmart will be at our next stop, Elko, which we will be driving to on Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;walmart.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
